>> Welcome everyone to
欢迎大家参加
the second session in today's program
今天节目的第二环节
focused on NDN
专注于命名数据网络（NDN）
for data-intensive applications,
针对数据密集型应用，
with five presentations that
将会有五场演讲，
are interrelated as you will discover
它们之间是相互关联的，正如你将会发现的。
from the first presentation by Edmund Yeh
来自Edmund Yeh的第一次演讲
on NDN for
~!@#$%^&*()
data-intensive science experiments.
数据密集型科学实验。
Edmund is a Professor
埃德蒙是一位教授
of Electrical and Computer
的电气与计算机工程
Engineering at North-Eastern University
东北大学的工程学院
with the research focus on a number
致力于研究大量
of communications and networking problems,
致力于通信和网络问题的研究，
including networking for data-intensive applications.
包括用于数据密集型应用的网络技术。
Edmund go-ahead and we need
Edmund, 请继续，我们需要~!@#$%^&*()
to watch the time because we
要注意时间，因为我们
have one hour for
我们有一个小时时间来进行
five presentations. Go ahead, please.
我们有一个小时时间来进行五个报告。请开始吧。
>> Thank you Lotfi, can you hear me?
>> 谢谢你，Lotfi，你能听到我说话吗？
>> Yes.
>> 是的。
>> Great. Thank you.
>> 很好。谢谢你。
Let me make sure that
让我确认一下
my slides are being shared or?
我的幻灯片正在分享中吗？
>> Not yet.
>> 还没有。
You have to share [OVERLAPPING] them again.
你得再分享一次[重叠]。
>> Can you see it now?
>> 现在你能看到了吗？
>> Yes. Just go full screen.
>> 是的。直接全屏就好。
>> Okay?
>> 好的？
>> Thank you very much for the introduction
>> 非常感谢您的介绍
and great to be here at NDN and calm.
非常高兴能来到NDN，感到很平静。
Last year I was here,
去年我在这里，
in fact talking about
实际上谈论着
NDN for data-intensive science.
NDN用于数据密集型科学。
In fact, I was talking about
实际上，我在谈论的是
a predecessor project
一个前期项目
This is the follow on project
这是后续项目。
which has also been funded by NSF for
该项目也得到了美国国家科学基金会的资助。
data-intensive science
数据密集型科学
experiments called N-DISE.
实验称为N-DISE。
I'm going to give an overview of what
我将概述我们尝试做的事情。
we're trying to do
我们正在尝试做
and some recent developments.
我们正在尝试做一些最近的发展。
As Lokhi mentioned,
正如洛奇提到的，
my talk will be followed
我的演讲将会有后续内容。
on by a number of tasks
将会有一系列的任务进行。
which expand on the themes mentioned here.
这些内容将对这里提到的主题进行扩展。
My slides are moving properly, I assume.
我的幻灯片应该在正常播放吧。
Data-intensive science
数据密集型科学
encompasses many different fields,
涵盖了许多不同的领域，
such as Large Hadron Collider.
像大型强子对撞机这样的。
This is high-energy physics,
这是高能物理学，
and this is the main example we're
这是我们正在处理的这个特定项目中的主要例子。
dealing in this particular project.
处理这个特定项目。
LSST, Large Synoptic Survey Telescope.
LSST，大型综合巡天望远镜。
The SKA Square Kilometer Array is
SKA，即平方公里阵列，是
astronomy and astrophysics fields which
天文学和天体物理学领域，它将会在每个夜晚处理大量数据。
take enormous amounts of data every night.
将会在每个夜晚处理大量数据。
Genomics is a new field which
基因组学是一个新兴领域，它
has also been looked
已经被研究过
at in this particular project.
已经被研究过，在这个特定的项目中。
All of these different fields,
这些不同的领域，
share similar challenges which
分享类似的挑战，它们
include how to index,
包括如何建立索引，
secure, store, distribute, analyze,
安全地保存、存储、分发、分析，
and learn from the data,
并从数据中学习，
and in the coordinated use of
并在协同使用中
computing storage and network resources.
计算存储和网络资源。
Even though these resources are substantial,
即便这些资源很充足，
when you have to deal with data sets and
当你必须处理数据集和~!@#$%^&*()
data volumes of the size
数据量的大小
that we're encountering here,
我们在这里遇到的，
you still have a lot of challenges.
你仍然面临着许多挑战。
Right now, the domain experts are dealing with
目前，领域专家们正在处理
these systems problems in
这些系统问题在
separate domains using incremental solutions
这些系统问题在独立的领域中使用渐进式解决方案developed often in isolation.
developed often in isolation.
这些系统问题通常是独立开发的。
There are many replicated efforts,
有很多重复的努力，
primarily due to the fact that
主要是因为
the architecture we're using today is now
我们今天使用的架构现在
quite suited to these applications.
非常适合这些应用程序。
What we're espousing here is a new approach.
我们在这里提倡的是一种新的方法。
A data-centric approach to
数据为中心的方法来
system and network design,
系统和网络设计，
and to provide system support through
并提供系统支持通过
the whole data life cycles
整个数据生命周期
from data production,
从数据产生，
naming the data, securing the data directly,
命名数据，直接保护数据，
delivering the data using names,
通过名称传递数据，
enabling scalable data retrieval,
实现可扩展的数据检索，
with native support for in-network caching,
具有对网络内缓存的原生支持，
automated joint caching and forwarding,
自动化的联合缓存和转发，
multicast delivery.
多播传送。
What we're trying to do is to
我们正在尝试去
develop a common framework for
我们正在尝试去开发一个通用框架来支持
a data-intensive science to support
数据密集型科学以支持
different kinds of application domains
不同类型的应用领域
using the same approach.
采用相同的方法。
This is all based on the NDN approach.
这一切都是基于NDN方法。
Now, this particular project was funded in
现在，这个特定的项目是在
2020 by the NSF CC* Start program.
2020年由NSF CC* Start计划资助。
It builds on the previous project
它是在之前的项目基础上发展起来的。
which I mentioned called SANDIE,
它我提到的名字叫做SANDIE，
which ran from 2017 to 2001.
该团队运行的时间是从2017年到2001年。
The team consists of Northeastern,
该团队由东北人组成，
where I'm leading the team,
在那里我领导着这个团队，
Caltech where Professor Harvey Newman
在加州理工学院，哈维·纽曼教授
from Caltech physics is leading the team.
来自加州理工学院物理系的哈维·纽曼教授正在领导这个团队。
UCLA, where the Co-PIs are,
加州大学洛杉矶分校，那里的联合主要研究员们，
Professor Lisa Zhang and
加州大学洛杉矶分校的联合主要研究员们，其中包括教授Lisa Zhang和教授Jason Cong，
professor Jason Cong,
教授Jason Cong，
they're leading the efforts on
他们正在带头进行努力
congestion control and FPGA acceleration,
拥塞控制和FPGA加速，
and Tennessee Tech where the Co-PI is
和田纳西科技大学，那里的联合首席研究员是
Susmit Shannigrahi who is
和田纳西科技大学，那里的联合首席研究员是Susmit Shannigrahi，他正在研究基因组学的应用。
looking at the application of genomics.
研究基因组学的应用。
We of course do this in partnership
我们当然是在合作伙伴关系中做这件事的
with the LHC teams,
与LHC团队一起，
the genomics collaborators in
与基因组学合作者一起，在
the NDN project team.
NDN项目团队。
But the challenges here,
但这里的挑战，
in particular the trouble trying to
尤其是试图解决的难题，
address is that LHC data volume is
地址的问题是LHC数据量是
such grow about 10 times due to
由于增长了大约10倍
the higher luminosity LHC
高亮度大型强子对撞机
which is set to start in 2027.
计划于2027年开始。
Therefore, we're looking at
因此，我们正在考察
another 10 times increase over and already
再增加10倍已经~!@#$%^&*()
there extremely high data volume-based.
它们基于极高的数据量。
We're also going to
我们还将会
get increased data complexity.
获得更复杂的数据。
We're also looking at
我们还在研究
human genome data and earth bio genome data,
人类基因组数据和地球生物基因组数据，
which is approaching the exabyte range.
接近艾字节量级。
All of these applications need to use
所有这些应用程序都需要使用
diverse computation storage,
多样化的计算存储，
networking resources.
多样化的计算存储，网络资源越来越需要。
the ability to use these diverse resources.
我们的方法是建立使用这些多样化资源的能力。
Our approach is to build
我们的方法是建立
a data-centric ecosystem,
一个以数据为中心的生态系统，
provide agile integrated,
提供敏捷集成的，
interoperable, scalable, robust,
互操作的、可扩展的、强健的，
and trustworthy solutions for
和可信赖的解决方案用于
heterogeneous data intensive domains.
异构数据密集型领域。
That is our larger goal.
这是我们的长远目标。
Now the near-term goal for the N-DISE project
现在N-DISE项目的近期目标是
is to deploy commission and commission
是要部署、投入使用并进行投产
the first prototype production ready
首个原型投产就绪
NDN based petascale data distribution caching,
基于NDN的千万亿级数据分发缓存，
access computation system,
基于NDN的千万亿级数据分发缓存，访问计算系统，服务于主要科学计划。
serve a major science programs.
服务于主要科学计划。
We're going to take
我们将要去
LHC high-energy physics as
我们将要去LHC高能物理作为
the leading target use case
领先的目标用例
, with bio genome,
，与生物基因组相结合，
human genome projects as
结合人类基因组项目，
the secondary use case,
次级用例，
and with ATLAS, LSST,
和ATLAS、LSST，
SKA as future use cases.
SKA作为未来的使用案例。
We're going to leverage the
我们将要利用
NDN protocols which have
我们将要利用NDN协议，它们已经开发出来并且已经
already been developed and have been
已经开发出来并且已经
discussed in previous sessions.
在之前的会议中讨论过。
High-throughput forwarding
高吞吐量转发
caching methods which have been
缓存方法已经
developed by the
由东北部和其他机构开发的~!@#$%^&*()
Northeastern and other institutions.
东北部和其他机构。
Containerization techniques,
集装箱化技术，
which are being developed at Caltech,
正在加州理工学院开发中，
integrated with FPGA acceleration subsystems
集成了 FPGA 加速子系统
which UCLA is looking at.
UCLA 正在研究的。
Our goal is to deliver LHC data over
我们的目标是通过
a wide area networks or throughputs
宽域网络或吞吐量
approaching 100 gigabits per second,
接近每秒100吉比特
and dramatically decrease download times
并显著减少下载时间
by using optimized caching.
通过使用优化的缓存。
We're very much going after performance here.
我们在这里非常追求性能。
For very large data volumes
对于非常大的数据量
using NDN approach.
使用NDN方法。
We are establishing a persistent testbed
我们正在建立一个持久的测试平台。
with high-performance NDN data cache servers.
配备高性能NDN数据缓存服务器。
We're going to demo that testbed at SC21,
我们将在SC21展示那个测试平台，
which is coming up in less than two weeks.
即将在不到两周的时间里举行。
Even after SC21 will keep
即将在不到两周的时间里举行，SC21之后仍将保持作为这个项目的持续性实验平台。
a persistent testbed for this project.
该项目的持续性实验平台。
Let me now just talk about
让我现在来谈谈
some recent developments with NDNs.
一些近期的NDN发展情况。
Let me know how much time I have left,
请告诉我我还剩下多少时间，
but I'll just try to go
但我会尽量快速地进行
through it relatively quickly.
我会相对快速地进行。
We've been looking at developing
我们一直在研究开发
the consumer and producer for NDN-DPDK.
消费者和生产者用于NDN-DPDK。
A new consumer-producer application
一款新的消费者-生产者应用程序
based on the NDNgo library,
基于NDNgo库，
which is developed by NIST
该系统是由美国国家标准与技术研究院（NIST）开发的。
, has been developed.
，已经开发完成。
Which replaces the extra NDN and OSS plugin,
已经取代了额外的NDN和OSS插件，
which I described last year,
去年我描述的，
by the SANDIE project.
由SANDIE项目实施。
For even better throughput,
为了进一步提高吞吐量，
we've developed new C++ NDNc library,
我们开发了新的C++ NDNc库，
with APIs for applications to communicate
通过应用程序通信的API
with the NDN-DPDK
通过NDN-DPDK与应用程序通信的API，期待使用memif，
forward to using the memif,
期待使用memif，
which is a shared memory package interface
它是一个共享内存包接口。
providing high-performance
提供高性能
packet transmission. This is all being done by
数据包传输。这一切都是由
the group at Caltech.
加州理工学院的团队。
We'll also be looking at containers
我们还将研究容器技术。
for NDN-DPDK and
NDN-DPDK的应用情况。
diverse server equipment and interfaces.
多种服务器设备和接口。
Specifically, using docker containers,
具体来说，使用 Docker 容器，
which allows you to host guest OS,
可以让你托管客户操作系统，
state restoration, easy upgrading.
状态恢复，轻松升级。
We're completely docker containerization
我们已完全实现了Docker容器化。
of the NDN-DPDK forwarder,
我们已完全实现了Docker容器化的NDN-DPDK转发器，
consumer, and producer.
消费者和生产者。
This is a joint effort between
这是一个联合努力，包括
Caltech and NIST in fact.
加州理工学院和美国国家标准与技术研究院，事实上。
We just also been looking
我们也一直在研究
at rate-based congestion control for NDN.
我们也一直在研究基于速率的NDN拥塞控制。This is headed by Professor [inaudible] UCLA.
This is headed by Professor [inaudible] UCLA.
这是由加州大学洛杉矶分校的[听不清]教授领导的。
The NDNs dynamic multipath forwarding and in
NDN的动态多路径转发和在
network caching renders
网络缓存呈现
the traditional congestion
传统的拥堵
control approach inapplicable.
控制方法不适用。
Therefore, we're developing
因此，我们正在开发
rate-based congestion control
基于速率的拥塞控制
where we're comparing
我们正在比较
the idea is to compare
我们的想法是进行比较
the consumer interest sending rate
消费者兴趣发送率
with the corresponding data arrival rate
与相应的数据到达率
to detect congestion,
以检测拥塞情况，
and then set the interest
然后设置兴趣率 accordingly
sending rate accordingly.
相应地设置发送率。
Professor Congs' group is looking at
康教授的团队正在研究
FPGA acceleration
Professor Kang's team is researching FPGA acceleration to accelerate the NDN forwarder.
to accelerate the NDN forwarder.
加速NDN转发器。
The initial focus of this effort
这项努力的初步重点
is on the input stage of the forwarder,
是在转发器的输入阶段，
where we're detecting a bottleneck.
我们正在检测到一个瓶颈。
The idea is to
我们的想法是
accelerate the hashing function and
加速哈希函数并且
lookup table used for thread dispatching.
用于线程调度的查找表。
For both of these areas,
对于这两个领域，
the congestion control and FPGA acceleration.
对于这两个领域，拥塞控制和FPGA加速。
There'll be talks coming up later in
稍后将有关于这两个领域，拥塞控制和FPGA加速的讨论会展开这些主题。
the session that expand on these themes.
将扩展这些主题的讨论会。
We're also looking at preliminary integration
我们还在初步探索集成
with genomics workflow.
的基因组学工作流程。
This is headed by Professor
这是由教授领导的Shannigrahi at Tennessee Tech。
Shannigrahi at Tennessee Tech.
Tennessee Tech的Shannigrahi。
We've tested docker containers
我们已经测试了Docker容器。
on the Pacific Research Platform,
在太平洋研究平台上，
PRP, and Google Cloud
PRP，在太平洋研究平台上，和Google云平台，通过与基因组学工作流程的结合使用。
by use with genomics workflows.
通过与基因组学工作流程的结合使用。
There's also
ongoing integration of containers with ~!@#$%^&*()
ongoing integration of containers with
持续集成容器与 ~!@#$%^&*()
Kubernetes-based systems or deployment
基于Kubernetes的系统或部署
and usage in genomics workflows.
和在基因组学工作流中的应用。
At Northeastern we've been focusing on
在东北大学，我们一直专注于
the NDN [OVERLAPPING] How many minutes, sorry?
抱歉，多少分钟？[重叠的部分]
>> One minute please.
>> 请稍等一分钟。
>> One minute okay. There I'll be fast.
>> 请稍等一分钟。我会很快的。
At Northeast we've been
在东北我们一直在~!@#$%^&*()
upgrading the local testbed.
升级本地测试环境。
We've implemented
我们已经实现了
a containerized NDN-DPDK forwarder,
我们已经实现了一个容器化的NDN-DPDK转发器，
the C-based consumer,
我们已经实现了一个容器化的NDN-DPDK转发器，基于C语言的消费者，以及NIST开发的文件服务器。
and file server developed by NIST.
和NIST开发的文件服务器。
We've upgraded the
我们已经升级了与NIST开发的文件服务器。
forwarding caching algorithm to
提供了转发缓存算法来
the latest NDN-DPDK forwarder with
最新的NDN-DPDK转发器与
performed extensive
进行了广泛的
throughput and cache latency tests.
进行了吞吐量和缓存延迟测试。
Now, I'm going to talk about
现在，我将要谈论
the WAN testbed,
WAN测试平台，
which we have put together.
我们已经组建了这个。
We've upgraded the Northeastern server
我们已经升级了东北部的服务器。
and moved it to
并将其迁移到
MGHPCC in order to
将其迁移到MGHPCC以便
access 100 gigabits
访问100吉比特
per second network bandwidth.
每秒网络带宽。
Caltech has upgraded
加州理工学院已经升级了
its connectivity working with StarLight.
它的连接性与StarLight合作得很好。
Now they have a 2
现在他们有一个2通过100吉比特连接到
by 100-gigabit connection to
the StarLight exchange point in
StarLight exchange point in
芝加哥的StarLight交换点在
Chicago and the StarLight SC21 booth.
芝加哥和StarLight SC21展位。
We purchased two new servers to be
我们购买了两台新服务器来~!@#$%^&*()
placed in Chicago and the SC21 booth.
我们在芝加哥和SC21展位放置了新的服务器。
We've added UCLA in
我们已经增加了加州大学洛杉矶分校
Tennessee Tech sites
田纳西科技站点
supporting 10-gigabit connections.
支持10吉比特连接。
In order to send the NDN
为了发送NDN~!@#$%^&*()
package directly in the network,
为了在网络中直接打包，
we've established VLAN
我们已经建立了VLAN
connections among the sites
站点之间的连接
in the testbed with support from Internet2,
在由Internet2支持的测试床中，
CENIC, ESnet, and UCSD.
CENIC、ESnet和UCSD。
This is the picture of our testbed here
这是我们测试平台的图片。
which we're going to use for SC21,
我们将会在SC21上使用这个，
also for the persistent testbed afterwards.
我们之后也会用它来作为持久的测试平台。
You can see we have Northeastern here,
你可以看到我们这里有东北大学。
StarLight in Chicago,
芝加哥的StarLight，
the SC21 StarLight booth here,
SC21 StarLight 展位在这里，
Tennessee Tech, Caltech we have
田纳西科技大学，加州理工学院我们有
two machines, and UCLA.
我们有两台机器，还有加州大学洛杉矶分校。
The idea is just
这个想法仅仅是
to looking forward to the SC21,
期待着即将在不到两周内举行的SC21，
which is coming up in less than two weeks.
即将在不到两周内到来。
We're going to demo N-DISE's data access
我们将要演示N-DISE的数据访问
distribution caching
分布式缓存
system over this testbed,
在这个测试平台上的系统，
focusing on throughput and
专注于吞吐量和
download latency experiments
下载延迟实验
with CMS datasets.
与CMS数据集一起。
We hope to get a very substantial increase in
我们希望获得非常可观的增长
performance for SC21 over SC19,
SC21相比SC19的表现，
which is two years ago.
这是两年前的事情。
We couldn't do it for 2020 because of COVID.
我们因为新冠疫情无法在2020年做到这一点。
Beyond SC21 we'll look
在SC21之后，我们将会关注以下话题。
at the following topics.
我们将会关注以下话题。
Let me just put it up there
我只是把它放在那里。
because of the limitation on time.
由于时间有限。
There are a number of things we want to
我们想要做许多事情
do after the SC21.
在SC21之后去做。
This project's going to
这个项目将会在SC21之后去做，持续至少再运行一年，
run for at least another year,
将继续运行至少再一年，
if not two years, so
如果不是两年的话，那么
there's a lot of work coming up.
将会有很多工作要做。
We're very excited and we hope
我们非常兴奋并且我们希望
to get a significant performance boost,
将会获得显著的性能提升，
that SC21 which is going to
将会获得显著的性能提升，那个SC21将会推动我们向前发展，我们当然会、、、
propel us forward, and we're, of course,
推动我们向前发展，我们当然、、、
seeking long-term collaboration with
寻求长期合作
domain science, networking,
领域科学、网络、
and computer systems communities
和计算机系统社群在这一努力中。
in this effort. Thank you very much.
在这一努力中。非常感谢您。
>> Thank you very much, Edmund.
>> 非常感谢你，埃德蒙。
For the sake of time, one quick question.
为了节省时间，我只问一个简单的问题。
By now, do you
到目前为止，你是否了解什么是吞吐量性能
know what throughput performance
你是否了解什么是吞吐量性能
you'll be able to show at SC21?
您能在SC21上展示吗？
>> Yeah, so a very good question.
是的，这是一个非常好的问题。
We're still working on it.
我们仍在努力中。
[LAUGHTER] I mean, you
~!@#$%^&*()
may encounter a lot of things while
在尝试做现场演示时，你可能会遇到很多事情。
you try to do live demos,
在尝试做现场演示时，
though we're pretty
尽管我们非常
confident we're going to get
我们非常有信心我们会得到
beyond 10 gigabits per second,
超过每秒10吉比特，
I think, but
我认为，不过
we are trying to push beyond that,
我们正在努力突破那个限制，
toward ultimate goal being
朝着最终目标努力
100 gigabits per second.
每秒100吉比特。
But also we're focusing
但我们也在专注
on decreasing the download latency,
在减少下载延迟上，
so there are two
所以这里有两个
different things going on here.
这里发生了不同的事情。
>> Thank you very much.
>> 非常感谢您。
>> Our next speaker is Catalin Iordache.
>> 我们的下一位演讲者是Catalin Iordache。
Catalin, you can
我们的下一位演讲者是Catalin Iordache。Catalin, 你可以开始分享你的屏幕了。
go ahead and start sharing your screen.
请继续并开始分享您的屏幕。
Catalin graduated from
Catalin 毕业于
the Polytechnic University of Bucharest
毕业于布加勒斯特理工大学
with a master's degree in
毕业并获得硕士学位
advanced computer architecture.
高级计算机架构。
Over the past few years,
在过去的几年里，
he's been a contractor for Caltech,
他一直是加州理工学院的一名承包商，
working on the SANDIE project,
他一直是加州理工学院的一名承包商，在SANDIE项目上工作，并且目前在N-DISE项目上。
and currently on the N-DISE project
并且目前在N-DISE项目上。
that he's going to tell us about it.
他将会告诉我们关于它的情况。
Catalin, go ahead, please.
卡塔琳，请开始吧。
>> Thank you, Lofti. Can you hear me?
>> 谢谢你，洛夫提。你能听见我说话吗？
>> Yes. Just [OVERLAPPING] good.
>> 是的。只是[重叠的声音]很好。
>> Perfect. Thank you very much,
>> 完美。非常感谢您，
and thank you for having me to
和感谢您邀请我参加
this community meeting.
参加这次社区会议。
It's my first time say,
这是我第一次说，
the past three years that I'm going
这是我第一次说，过去的三年我将要去讨论的事情。
to talk about what I'm
将要去讨论我正在做的事情。
doing by using NDN to these projects.
利用NDN来进行这些项目的工作。
The topic today will be this NDNc,
今天的主题将是这个NDNc，
what it is, and why we are doing it?
它是什么，以及我们为什么要这么做？
In order to explain it,
为了解释它，
I would first like to say that
我首先想说，
they're both working for the SANDIE project,
他们俩都在为SANDIE项目工作，
project at this moment.
此时该项目。
The main goal of
此时该项目的主要目标是
both projects on
此时该项目的主要目标是both projects on应用方面始终是~!@#$%^&*()
the application side was always to
应用方面始终是
deploy NDN in
部署NDN在~!@#$%^&*()
large-scale
大规模
data-intensive science experiments
数据密集型科学实验
such as LHC, high-energy physics.
例如LHC，高能物理学。
This has always been our goal,
这一直是我们的目标，
and today I'm going to first show you
今天我首先要向你们展示
how currently the data is
今天我首先要向你们展示的是，如何目前数据正在被访问和传递，
being accessed and delivered,
正在被访问和传递，
that CMS, one of
正在被访问和传递的CMS，其中一个大型实验就是我看到的。
the two large experiments that I see.
我看到的两个大型实验。
Then how NDN application
would look like in such an environment,
would look like in such an environment,
在这样的环境下看起来会是什么样的，
at least the way we envision it.
至少按照我们所设想的方式。
Then I will talk about the triple performance
接下来我将讨论三重性能
of such an application, and finally,
的这种应用，最后，
this will lead up to what is NDNc,
这将引出NDNc是什么，
and the future plans for this.
以及未来的计划。
First, how is data access today at CMS?
首先，今天在CMS中数据访问是怎样的？
we have this diagram
我们有这张图表。
where at the bottom you have
在底部您有
the side B and site C.
在底部您有B侧和C地点。As you can see both sides have ~!@#$%^&*()
As you can see both sides have
如您所见，两边都有
access to some storage,
访问某些存储空间，
and the storage contains
和存储空间包含
data from the CMS experiment.
来自CMS实验的数据。
I mean, alongside site B you
我的意思是，除了B地点，你还有其他地点以及相同的~!@#$%^&*()
also have a number of sites and the same
也有许多地点和相同的
for site C. Although
对于C地点。尽管
these sites are connected
这些站点是相连的
to or so-called Regional XRootD Redirector,
至或所谓的区域XRootD重定向器，
which knows about all of the sites below it,
它了解其下所有站点的信息，
and also about the Global Redirector.
以及关于全球重定向器的信息。
In this diagram,
在这张图表中，
you have a redirector in US and one in EU.
你在美国和欧盟都有一个重定向器。
In this case for us site A,
在这种情况下，对于我们的网站A来说，
or here in the left-hand corner
或者在左手边的角落里
is where the user applications runs,
是用户应用程序运行的地方，
where the scientists are actually running
是科学家们实际运行(他们的科学应用程序的地方)，
their scientific application,
他们的科学应用程序，
scientific data at CMS.
科学数据在CMS中。
In this case, we have two applications.
在这种情况下，我们有两个应用程序。
In the first case,
在第一种情况下，
the application actually requests the data.
应用程序实际上会请求数据。
The first thing it will do,
它首先会做的事情是，
this application would
这个应用程序会
actually look locally,
实际上会在本地查找，
and it resides there,
它就存在于那里，
then there's no need
那么就没有必要了
to search for it further.
那么就没有必要再进一步搜索了。
In the first case,
在第一种情况下，
you will see that the data
您会看到数据
it's actually at site A.
它实际上在A地点。
But then in the second case,
但在第二种情况下，
these are the application,
这些是应用程序，
actually looks for the data again
实际上再次查找数据
local at site A, but it doesn't find it.
它在A地点进行本地搜索，但没有找到。
What it does after that is go to step 2,
它之后做的是进行第二步，
and that is to ask
它之后做的是进行第二步，那就是询问它的区域重定向器关于一个网站，
its Regional Redirector about a site,
它的区域重定向器关于一个网站，
what the data can be.
它的数据可能是什么。
This redirector would look at
这个重定向器会查看
site B to see if the file is in there,
如果文件在那里，它会查看站点B。
if not, then it will go to Global Redirector.
如果没有，那么它会转到全局重定向器。
This redirector would look at
这个重定向器会查看
the director at EU,
这位欧盟的主管，
or maybe other regions as well.
或许也包括其他地区。
When the data is found,
当数据被找到时，
finally, in this case,
最终，在这种情况下，
it's site C, then the application site,
如果是C地点，那么申请地点，
they will be notified that
他们将会被通知说
here is the IP where
这是IP地址在哪里，
the data is, in this case,
这种情况下，数据是
it's site C, and then the application would
在这种情况下，数据是来自C站点的，然后应用程序将会
connect to that IP and
连接到那个IP并且
actually read the data.
实际上读取数据。
Like I said, these applications
像我说的，这些应用程序
are called XRootD.
被称为XRootD。
What is actually XRootD?
XRootD是一个被称为XRootD的框架，它是~!@#$%^&*()
It's a framework, and it's
它是一个框架，它是~!@#$%^&*()
basically the defined management tool
基本上是定义的管理工具
that's used at server
用于服务器上
for distributing and reading data and so on.
用于分发和读取数据等操作。
because it's a framework
因为它是一个框架。
which they also enables
它们同样也能够使得开发者实现各种类型
developers to implement various types
开发者实现各种类型
of plug-ins for it.
的插件。
For example, you can develop
例如，您可以开发
your own file system plug-in for this,
您可以为此开发您自己的文件系统插件，
or caching plug-in or a
或者是缓存插件或者是一个
security plug-in, and so on.
安全插件等等。
I mean the list is big.
我的意思是列表很长。
But it's a C++ framework,
但它是一个C++框架，
and the source code it's open source.
而且它的源代码是开源的。
But they also develop something in Golang,
但他们也在用Golang开发一些东西，
but it's just at the beginning.
但这只是刚开始。
In our case, we
我们的情况下，
wanted to develop this plug-in,
我们想要开发这个插件，
which is called an Open
它被称为一个开放的
Storage System plug-in,
存储系统插件，
and it's actually implementation
和它实际的实现
of the file system.
的文件系统。
Its core is just
它的核心仅仅是
the C++ dynamic library that exports
导出的C++动态库
just one single symbol
只是一个单一的符号
in order for these to get to
为了让这些能够到达
know how to load this library.
了解如何加载这个库。
In the implementation of
在实施过程中
the plug-ins actually needs to
插件实际上需要
offer implementation for
提供实施方案
each posting slices system then co-created.
每个帖子都是系统切分后共同创作的。
For example, you have probably implementation
例如，你可能已经实施了
for open, for close, for read,
用于打开，用于关闭，用于读取，
for opendir, readdir,
用于打开目录，用于读取目录，
and all the other posting plugins and calls.
以及所有其他发布插件和调用。
This is basically the plug-in,
这基本上就是插件，
and what we envision is actually to
我们设想的实际上是要
embed an NDN consumer,
嵌入一个NDN消费者，
in this issue the plug-in.
在这个问题中嵌入一个插件。
That consumer should be able to translate
该消费者应该能够进行翻译。
between the file system call to an NDN name,
在文件系统调用和NDN名称之间，
then compose on interest with that name,
然后根据那个名称构建兴趣包，
send it over an NDN network,
将其通过NDN网络发送过去。
and the other end would have producer
将其通过NDN网络发送过去，并且另一端会有生产者对数据进行访问。
that have access to the data.
它们能够访问数据。
They will send the data back,
它们将会发送回数据，
and then the consumer will read the data.
然后消费者将读取数据。
We'll verify that data is valid,
我们将验证数据是否有效，
and then put it back to the XRootD framework.
然后将其重新放回到XRootD框架中。
[NOISE] In our case,
在我们的情况下，
we did this,
我们做了这个，
and we also had to came
我们还必须得出了一个命名方案。
For example, for B
例如，对于B
open or fstat file system calls,
打开或fstat文件系统调用，
we have this name,
我们有这个名字，
which the prefix is NDN XRootD.
其前缀为NDN XRootD。
Then you have the meta,
然后你有了元数据，
which basically requests a meta-package,
它基本上请求了一个元包，
which is also requested when
它也是在请求时
the file system is open or fstat.
文件系统是打开的还是fstat。
The data packet of
数据包
interest contains a bunch
兴趣包含了大量
of information about the file.
包含了大量关于文件的信息。
Then basically in the green,
那么基本上在绿色区域里，
you have the file path.
你有文件路径。
Now for example, for
现在，例如，对于
the read file system call,
读取文件系统调用，
there's a different name.
有一个不同的名字。
We have the same prefix and the XRootD,
我们有相同的前缀和XRootD，
you have the hyper, and then you have
你有超级，然后你有
the segment number and
段号和
the version of the file.
文件的版本。
Then the producer on the other hand
那么另一方面的制作人
will not to translate
不会翻译
the segment number to an offset
段号到偏移量
in the corresponding file.
在相应的文件中。
This is what we did already.
这就是我们已经做过的。
The first implementation of this was using
这是我们第一次实现这个功能时所使用的~!@#$%^&*()
the NDNCX library with
这个NDNCX库与~!@#$%^&*()
NFD and we run a bunch of tests on that,
NFD我们在上面运行了一系列测试，
and all this we're stuck
我们被困在这里了。
below one gigabit per second performance.
低于每秒一千兆比特的性能。
As you can see in these two diagrams,
如您在这两张图表中所见，
in the first one above,
在上面的第一张图表中，
once we apply the interface on the delay,
在我们对延迟应用接口后，
the throughput also went down.
吞吐量也下降了。
It was working. It was a good experiment,
它在运作。这是一个成功的实验，
but the trucker performance wasn't there.
但卡车司机的表现并不理想。
We also compared our consumer that was
我们还比较了我们的消费者，它是
embedded in the library
嵌入在库中
with the NDN put in chunks,
与NDN分块嵌入在库中，
and they actually performed
他们实际上表现出了
better than those applications.
他们实际上表现出了比那些应用程序更好。But either way,
But either way,
但无论如何，
the performance was not that good.
表现并不是很好。
But we continue to
但我们继续
test this plug-in just to
测试这个插件只是为了
see that the NDN can work,
看到NDN可以工作，
and one of our colleagues, Justice.
和我们的一位同事，贾斯蒂斯。
he run a bunch of tests and compared
他进行了一系列测试并进行了比较。
the NDN with multiple storage solutions.
在这张图表中，您将看到具有多种存储解决方案的NDN。
In this diagram, you will see
在这张图表中，您将看到
the success rate of CMS jobs,
在这张图表中，您将看到CMS工作的成功率，those user application that I
those user application that I
was talking about earlier.
was talking about earlier.
我之前提到的。
Here's the success versus failed rate.
这是成功与失败的比率。
He compared it against
他将其与...进行了比较。
Ceph, against Hadoop,
Ceph相比于Hadoop，
against using
反对使用
differentiated directors one at Fermilab,
分别任职于费米实验室的不同董事，
one at Caltech, one at CERN,
分别任职于加州理工学院和欧洲核子研究中心，
and against all different kinds of caches.
和针对所有不同类型的缓存。
Here in the right, it's NDN.
在这边右边，这是NDN。
We can see that at least for this test,
我们可以看到，至少对于这个测试来说，
it did perform good.
它的表现确实不错。
Looking forward, you can
展望未来，你可以
also see that the time to complete
也可以看出完成这些工作所需的时间
all these 269 jobs was fairly
可以完成这些工作所需的时间平均使用NDN库
average using the NDN library
平均使用NDN库
one compared to the other solution.
与另一种解决方案相比。
The idea is good, but then we know
这个想法不错，但随后我们知道
that if you want to
我们知道，如果你想要
use thousands and thousands of jobs,
使用成千上万的工作岗位，
which happens in production,
这在生产中发生，
then the triple would have been better.
那么三重奏本会更好。
We continue to search
我们继续寻找
for performance per our applications.
为了我们应用程序的性能表现。
We knew that the NFD
我们知道NFD~!@#$%^&*()
was one of the main bottlenecks.
是主要的瓶颈之一。
Luckily at the same time, I think
幸运的是，同时我认为
the NDN team at
NDN团队在
NIST was already working
NIST已经在进行工作
on the NDN-DPDK forwarder.
在NDN-DPDK转发器上。
As soon as they find about that,
他们一发现那件事，
we implemented
我们实现了
our own DPDK consumer and
我们自己的DPDK消费者和
producer applications
生产者应用程序
which were generating a file transfer.
它们正在生成一个文件传输。
We demo that at SuperComputing 2019.
我们在2019年的超级计算会议上演示了那个。
We got a performance
我们获得了一个性能
of about 6.7 gigabits
大约6.7吉比特
per second over a wide area network.
每秒在广域网络上。
But then the drawback for this was just
但随之而来的缺点就是
the fact that there
但事实上，
wasn't any NDN API for us,
没有适用于我们的NDN API，
so we had to implement
所以我们不得不自己实现
everything almost from scratch.
几乎从零开始。
For us, this is not the way to go.
对我们来说，这不是正确的方法。
We want to focus on other things,
我们想要专注于其他事情，
not rebuilding NDN from scratch.
我们不打算从头开始重建NDN。
But the worst thing
但最糟糕的事情
for us was actually to deploy
对我们来说，实际上是要部署
these applications on the machine
需要在机器上部署这些应用程序。
at CMS because they
需要在CMS上部署这些应用程序，因为它们全部使用旧中心的机器。
all use old-center machines.
全部使用旧中心的机器。
It's a big hustle to actually start
实际上开始是一件很费劲的事情。
the DPDK applications on this kind
这种类型的DPDK应用程序
of operating system and so and so.
的操作系统等等。
Although the performance was
虽然表现是
super good and promising,
虽然表现是非常好且有前途的，
the actual useability of
实际的可用性
it and also
它以及还有
the development was not that good.
发展并不是那么好。
We continue to look forward and further to
我们继续向前看，更进一步地探索。
this NDNgo library that
这个NDNgo库是
was also developed by NIST.
也是由NIST开发的。
Meeting goal, we developed
我们开发的会议目标，
the consumer and producer for
消费者和生产者
that as well in [inaudible]
~!@#$%^&*()
just to simulate file transfers.
只是为了模拟文件传输。
We got around 2.2
我们获得了大约2.2
gigabits per second with just one consumer.
我们获得了大约2.2吉比特每秒的速度，仅仅是来自一个用户。We expecting maybe more because it already~!@#$%^&*()
We expecting maybe more because it already
我们期待会有更多，因为它已经~!@#$%^&*()
used many which is the interface
使用了许多这是接口
that you can connect to NDN-DPDK.
但后来我们了解到这个库可以连接到NDN-DPDK。
But then we learned that this library
但后来我们了解到这个库
wasn't actually built for this kind of stuff,
但后来我们了解到这个库并不是为了这类事情而建造的，
but more for management or the forwarder.
但更多是为了管理或货代。
This is the results
这是结果
for the SuperComputing 2019.
我们在2019年的超级计算会议上的表现。
We have the performance of
我们的表现
about 6.7 gigabits per second.
大约每秒6.7吉比特。
The experiment was only for three hours,
实验仅持续了三个小时，
again with the DPDK
再次涉及DPDK
consumer-producer applications.
消费者-生产者应用程序。
Then we arrive at [inaudible] where,
那么我们到达了[听不清]处，
as Professor Yen mentioned earlier,
正如严教授先前提到的，
our goal is to
我们的目标是实现每秒100吉比特的速度。
achieve 100 gigabits per second.
实现每秒100吉比特的速度。
That can be given a aggregate throughput.
这可以提供总体吞吐量。
We came up with this diagram here
我们在这里设计了这张图。
where you have an NDN network,
你有一个NDN网络，
you're using NDN-DPDK forwarders.
你正在使用NDN-DPDK转发器。
Then at one end,
那么在一端，
you have Ceph that have
您有Ceph存储系统，它有
access to the CMS data.
访问CMS数据的权限。
There you have host with
您有一台主机，它具有~!@#$%^&*()
dedicated NICs where we
专用网卡在我们
also run docker containers,
也可以运行Docker容器，
where you have
可以运行Docker容器的地方，NDN-DPDK转发器运行在
the NDN-DPDK forwarder running in
一个Docker容器中运行的NDN-DPDK转发器
one docker container and
一个Docker容器和
uses that network card.
使用那个网络卡。
Then you maybe have
那么你可能有
a producer that uses
一个使用的生产者
memif, it's written C++.
memif（内存接口），它是用C++编写的。
It's fast and it can access the storage,
它速度快且可以访问存储空间，
but then also can use other solution of
但也可以使用其他解决方案
other file transfer servers
其他文件传输服务器
like one that will be later presented.
像一个稍后将会介绍的那样。
On the left side, you have the consumers.
在左边，你有消费者。
Again, this is on the left-hand side.
这又是在左手边。
You can have one or more host machines.
你可以拥有一台或多台主机。
Then again you have one dedicated NIC
然后你还有一块专用的网卡。
that's going to be used by
将被用于
the NDN-DPDK forwarder
NDN-DPDK转发器
running the docker container.
运行Docker容器。
Then another docker containers will have
那么其他的Docker容器将会
actually XRootD plugins which
实际上是XRootD插件，它们
embed NDN consumer in that.
嵌入NDN消费者至其中。
Then at that side,
那么在那边，
we have thousands and thousands of
我们有成千上万的
CMS jobs that are
我们有成千上万的CMS作业正在访问这个XRootD应用程序。
accessing this XRootD applications.
正在访问这个XRootD应用程序。
Then they will send
然后他们将发送
and request data across the network.
并跨网络请求数据。
Then what is NDNc? Sorry.
那么NDNc是什么？抱歉。
>> A minute, I'm running that file.
>> 等一下，我正在运行那个文件。
>> Sorry. Yeah, the NDNc
抱歉。是的，NDNc
is basically a small library,
基本上是一个小型库，
a set of functions that actually
一组实际上的功能集合，
adds ndn-cxx support back to
将ndn-cxx支持重新加入到
NDN-DPDK and it uses
NDN-DPDK并且它使用
memif shared memory packet interface.
内存共享数据包接口 memif。
At the moment, we have already implemented
目前，我们已经实现了
the GraphQL client that enables
我们实现的GraphQL客户端，它使得
us to configure the forwarder,
我们配置转发器，
like creating a face, inserting a FibEntry,
像创建一个面孔，插入一个FibEntry，
or deleting
或删除
some information from the forwarder.
来自货运代理的一些信息。
At the moment, like I said,
目前，正如我所说，
has a transport layer which
目前，正如我所说，有一个传输层，它是memif但是它是单线程的，
is memif but is single-threaded,
是memif，但它是单线程的，
also has a face object that enables us to
也有一个面向对象，它允许我们能够
send one or more packets
发送一个或多个数据包
at the time of the network.
在网络时期。
It also offers PIT token support,
它还提供了PIT令牌支持，
something that ndn-cxx doesn't do.
它还提供了PIT令牌支持，这是ndn-cxx所不具备的功能。Yeah, we also have
Yeah, we also have
是的，我们还有
some abstract classes that you can use
一些你可以使用的抽象类
to base your customer-producer application
来构建你的消费者-生产者应用程序
upon and also have some congestion window,
在此之上还应有一些拥塞窗口控制，
retransmissions in there already.
在此之前已经有了重传机制。
We have a fixed window and a AIMD.
我们有一个固定窗口和一个加性增大乘性减小(AIMD)机制。
We plan to add more soon.
我们计划不久后会添加更多内容。
We also have a logger and we also have CMake
我们还有一个日志记录器，同时也使用了CMake。
and Dockerfile for deploying all of this.
我们还为部署所有这些内容编写了Dockerfile。
Using the NDNc,
我们使用了NDNc，
we already build two applications.
我们已经构建了两个应用程序。
We build the PING consumer and also build
我们已经构建了PING消费者应用程序，并且还构建了
a high transfer consumer
高效传输消费者
and producer applications.
和生产者应用程序。
So far so good.
目前为止一切都好。
Just with one consumer,
仅凭一个消费者，
the maximum is 4.3 gigabits per
秒的最大传输速率是4.3千兆比特。
second this in 6,600 bytes per payload size.
每秒传输6,600字节的有效载荷大小。
We think that this is the way to go moving
我们认为这是前进的方向，并且我们希望在此基础上继续发展。
forward and we like to build upon this.
我们认为这是向前迈进的方向，并且我们希望在此基础上继续构建。
Like I said, we would
像我说的，我们会
like to continue to bring more
像继续带来更多
benchmarking to
提高标杆以
identify possible bottlenecks and maybe
识别可能的瓶颈，也许
implement some of our own method and not use
实现我们自己的一些方法，而不使用
everything from ndn-cxx,
实现我们自己的一些方法，而不使用ndn-cxx的所有内容，增加多线程支持。
add multiple-threaded support.
增加多线程支持。
Since we asked also to make a wish list,
既然我们也被要求制作一个愿望清单，
I just made one,
我刚做了一个，
and that is to actually,
实际上，
maybe more would like
也许会有更多人愿意
to join our efforts, I don't know.
加入我们的努力，我不知道。
Maybe there are
也许有一些其他人在这个社区
that are also like us
可能也和我们一样
looking for throughput performance.
寻找吞吐量性能。
It would be nice to get in touch and
一起工作将会很好。
work on this together. Thank you.
一起工作在这个项目上。谢谢。
>> Great, thanks. There's some discussion on
>> 很好，谢谢。有一些讨论在
the Slack channel asking about
the Slack 频道上有人在询问关于
how were you able to
你是如何能够
achieve performance more than five gigabits.
实现超过五千兆比特的性能。
You showed 6.7, right?
你显示的是6.7，对吗？
>> Yes.
是的。
>> One good question is,
>> 一个好问题是，
what's on top of
>> 一个好问题是，what's on top of~!@#$%^&*()
your list to booth
你的展位清单
the throughput performance?
吞吐量性能？
What's the next bottleneck
下一个瓶颈是什么？
you're going to address?
你打算解决吗？
>> Yes, this is a good question.
是的，这是一个好问题。
This is a network that is new,
这是一个新的网络，
we can't afford for about 5-4 months.
我们大约有4到5个月的时间承担不起这个费用。
It's still young, it's a young project.
它还很年轻，这是一个新项目。
Like I said, we need to do benchmarking
像我说的，我们需要做基准测试。
a lot to understand what the bottlenecks are.
我们需要了解很多东西才能明白瓶颈在哪里。
Of course, at the moment
当然，在目前
it's all single-threaded.
它是单线程的。
The easiest thing to do is go multi-threaded.
最简单的方法就是采用多线程。
But I think until we do that,
但我认为在我们做那件事之前，
we would like to
我们希望能够
get the best performance
获得最佳性能
out of the single-thread.
脱离单线程。
Yes, we don't know
是的，我们不知道。
exactly if we have
确切地说，如果我们有
bottlenecks and where those are,
瓶颈在哪里以及这些瓶颈是什么，
but we need to do more testing.
但我们需要做更多的测试。
>> Okay, good. Thanks again.
>> 好的，很好。再次感谢。
You can continue the discussion
您可以继续讨论
on the Slack channel.
在Slack频道上。
There are a few things you can address there.
您可以在那里处理一些事情。
Our next speaker is Sichen Song.
我们的下一位演讲嘉宾是宋思辰。
Sichen is a master's student at
宋思辰是一名硕士研究生，在
UCLA and is a research assistant
宋思辰是一名硕士研究生，在加州大学洛杉矶分校担任研究助理，在互联网研究实验室从事NDN的研究工作。
in the Internet Research Lab working on NDN
在互联网研究实验室从事NDN的研究工作。
including congestion control
包括拥塞控制
and he does mitigation.
他还负责缓解措施。
He's going to tell us about his work on
他将向我们介绍他的工作内容，包括
congestion control in
网络拥塞控制
support and this project.
支持这个项目。
Go ahead, please, Sichen.
请继续，Sichen。
>> Thanks. Can you see my screen?
>> 谢谢。你能看到我的屏幕吗？
Is it present?
是否在场？
>> Yeah, good to go. Yes.
>> 是的，可以开始了。是的。
>> Is it present?
>> 它在场吗？
>> It's on screen, yes.
>> 是的，它在屏幕上。
>> Okay. Thanks. I'm Sichen from UCLA,
>> 好的，谢谢。我是来自加州大学洛杉矶分校的Sichen，
I'm going to talk about our work,
我将会讲述我们的工作，
our rate based congestion control.
我们的基于速率的拥塞控制。
Lets start with a problem description.
让我们从问题描述开始。
Congestion control algorithms in
TCP/IP generally rely on window-based mechanisms.
TCPIP are window-based in general.
TCP/IP 通常基于窗口机制。
Those algorithms are
这些算法是
estimatings of pipe size,
估算管道尺寸，
which is a maximum amount
的最大数量
of bytes inside
字节内
the network without killing it.
不会破坏网络的情况下。
Adjust the condenser window
调整冷凝器窗口
two p's a pipe size.
两个P表示管道尺寸。
In India, there's
在印度，有
dynamic multi-pass poverty and
动态多遍次贫困和
caching that destroys
破坏性的缓存
the concept of pipe size.
管道尺寸的概念。
So we hope to work on
所以我们希望致力于工作
a congestion control algorithm
一种拥塞控制算法
that battlefields named data networking.
该战场名为命名数据网络。
The algorithm should be adaptive to
算法应该能够适应
the available bandwidth or our active paths,
可用带宽或我们的活动路径，
and also it should be
并且它还应该是
insensitive to round trip time variations.
对往返时间的变化不敏感。
We hope to start this effort by letting
我们希望通过让
end-consumers do measurements and
最终消费者进行测量和
adjust these transmission rates.
调整这些传输率。
We have four goals in importance order.
我们有四个按重要性排序的目标。
The designs should be
设计应当是
able to prevent long queue
能够防止长队形成
building up and to have high bandwidth usage.
形成积压并且具有高带宽使用量。
Not to rely on packet loss
不依赖于数据包丢失
as the congestion signal.
作为拥塞信号。
Lastly, it should give a good fairness.
最后，它应该保证良好的公平性。
At least there should not be starvation.
至少不应该有人挨饿。
For this talk, I hope
为了这次演讲，我希望
to talk about our work in
为了这次演讲，我希望谈论我们在工作中的进展情况。
progress of this part
这部分的进展情况
and I'll talk about our current design.
我会讲述我们当前的设计。
So congestion control and also about
所以关于拥塞控制以及相关内容
a interesting observation of
一个有趣的观察结果
measurement interference
测量干扰
between consumers and their caching.
在消费者和他们的缓存之间。
Let's start with basic idea of the design.
让我们从设计的基本概念开始。
is to control the interests sending
是为了控制发送方的利益。
rates instead of the congestion window
使用速率控制而非拥塞窗口
and we do it round by round.
我们一轮接一轮地进行。
At each round restart
我们每一轮重新开始时，
by keep sending us the same,
每次都不断地向我们发送相同的内容，
the consumers sending at
消费者以相同的发送速率
illustrated by this blue line.
用这条蓝线表示。
This keeps going for
这一直持续进行着
a maximum round-trip delay
最大往返时延
among our forwarding paths.
在我们的转发路径中。
This allows the consumer
这使得消费者
to observe the effect of
观察效果
these rates at our multiple folding paths.
这些速率在我们的多条折叠路径上。
Afterwards, a measurement of
随后，一项测量
data arrival rates will
数据到达率将会
start for a matter of time.
开始计时。
During this time, the consumer
在这段时间里，消费者
tries to keep sending
尝试继续发送
while getting
尝试获取
an accurate data arrival rate measurements.
准确的数据到达率测量。
Then later,
在这些部分结束之后，
the consumer needs to make
消费者需要做出
the decision of whether there's congestion.
消费者需要做出是否有拥堵的决定。
This is done by
这是通过
thresholding the difference between
阈值化差异
the data arrival rate measurement
数据到达率测量
and the current interest sending rate.
以及当前的利率发送率。
If there's more or less the same,
如果有或多或少相同，
the consumer would think there's
消费者会认为有~!@#$%^&*()
no congestion and continue to increase
没有拥堵并且持续增长
is interest sending rate following
利率走势是否遵循~!@#$%^&*()
a cubic curve similar
类似于立方曲线
to the idea of TCP cubic.
到TCP立方的概念。
After keeping going without congestion,
在持续无拥堵地前行后，
eventually the consumer will get above
最终，消费者将得到更上一层的
the network capacity and
Ultimately, consumers will experience an improved level of network capacity and a congestion will be caused.
a congestion and will be caused.
将会引起拥堵。
When this happens,
当这种情况发生时，
it is expected that the consumer will
预计消费者将会
observe his interest sending
观察他显示出的兴趣
rates will be faster than
速率将会更快于
the data arrival rate
数据到达率
and by that holding their difference,
并因此保持它们之间的差异，
the consumer will be able to detect
消费者将能够察觉
the congestion at this point
在这一点上的拥堵情况
and the trigger a multiplicative decrease
触发了成倍的减少
to avoid the congestion.
为了避免拥堵。
Of course, network congestions are not
当然，网络拥堵并不总是由这个消费者引起的。
always caused by this consumer,
并不总是由这个消费者引起的，
but can also be caused by external factors.
但也可能是由外部因素引起的。
When congestions are
当交通拥堵时
caused by external factors.
造成的外部因素。
For example, a bottleneck
例如，一个瓶颈
bandwidths suddenly dropped,
带宽突然下降了，
we expect as a consumer we'll see
我们作为消费者期待会看到
some unexpected drop of
一些意想不到的下降
data arrival rates and to
数据到达率以及如何
react with congestion as
在拥堵时迅速作出反应以及如何尽可能快地
quick as possible when
迅速地当
the consumer observes a
消费者观察到一个~!@#$%^&*()
data arrival rates drop.
数据到达率下降。
It will also trigger
它也将触发
a multiplicative decrease
乘法减少
to a wider congestion.
扩展到更广泛的拥堵。
With this basic idea,
有了这个基本概念，
I will talk about
我将会讲述~!@#$%^&*()
an interesting observation
一个有趣的观察
in our evaluation process,
在我们的评估过程中，
which is measurement interference
这是测量干扰。
between consumers and their caching.
在消费者和他们的缓存之间。
Let's start with the scenario we are using.
让我们从我们正在使用的场景开始。
We have two consumers,
我们有两个消费者，
C1 and C2 fetch
C1和C2获取
the same data object in order.
按顺序获取相同的数据对象。
C2 started early, so it's
C2提早开始，所以它能够最初取得更多进展。
able to make more progress initially.
能够最初取得更多进展。
The forwarder here F1 has
这里的货运代理F1有
a very large content store.
这里的货运代理F1有一个非常大的内容存储库。我们期望在C1启动后，
We expect that after C1 has started,
我们期望在C1启动后，
it will initially be satisfied by
在最初阶段将会由此得到满足
the orders cache that has
在最初阶段将会由此得到满足, 订单缓存已经有了，其带宽对转发器是
its bandwidth to the forwarder is
sufficient for the initial phase, as there is already an order cache, and its bandwidth to the forwarder is much higher than the bandwidth to
much higher than the bandwidth to
的带宽要远高于向
the producer.
的带宽要远高于向 the producer. It will eventually bring ~!@#$%^&*()
It will eventually bring
It will eventually bring ~!@#$%^&*()
the cache and be able to catch up
缓存并能够赶上
with the other consumer that started
与其他早先开始的消费者一起
early and then be satisfied as a producer.
与其他早先开始的消费者一起，早早地然后作为生产者感到满意。
Our evaluations shows in that our design,
我们的评估显示，在我们的设计中，
the consumer C1 will keep
消费者C1将会保持
satisfied by the cache most
满足于缓存大部分
of the time in the steady-state,
在稳态中的大部分时间里，
so he is not able to fully catch up.
所以他没能完全赶上。
We hope to understand why.
我们希望理解其中的原因。
So we take a look at
所以我们来看一下
the C1's perspective to
我们来看一下C1的观点，观察接下来会发生什么。
observe what's going to happen.
观察接下来会发生什么。
Of course, initially, C1
当然，最初的话，C1
will be satisfied by the content store and
将由内容存储满足并且
it's observed round-trip delay
观察到的往返延迟
will be round-trip delay
将会是往返延迟
to the cache and
到缓存中
if C1 eventually catches up,
如果C1最终赶上了，
it will be satisfied by the producer and
它将会被生产者满足，并且
the round trip delays events this
这将导致往返延迟事件。
will be the round-trip delay to the producer.
这将是对生产者的往返延迟。
However, there is a stage in the middle.
然而，中间还有一个阶段。
In this stage, by
在这个阶段，通过
the time C1's interest
C1的兴趣时刻
goes to the forwarder,
前往货运代理商，
the early starter's interests
早起者的利益
have already passed the forwarder,
已经通过了货代。
so forwarder just aggregates that interests.
所以货代只是聚合了那些利益。
However, the early starter C2 state
然而，早期的C2状态
at that time had not returned to cache.
那时还没有回到缓存中。
So C1 is not able to be satisfied by cache.
所以C1无法得到缓存的满足。
So C1 will wait a little bit
所以C1会稍微等一会儿
for the data solicited by
为了请求的数据
the other consumer to come back and then
其他消费者回来然后
be used to satisfy its own interests.
用来满足自身的利益。
We can see that two round-trip delay,
我们可以看到两次往返延迟，
similar observes, is between
观察到的相似之处，在于……
the two other end states.
两个其他的终止状态。
Also, the round-trip delay
还有，往返延迟
it observes depends on
它观察到的取决于
the progress difference
进度差异
between the two consumers.
在两个消费者之间。
Since C1 is trying to catch up and
由于C1正在试图追赶并且
it's sending faster than the other consumer,
它的发送速度比另一个消费者快，
we would think that as a round-trip delay,
我们会认为那是一个往返延迟，
we'll do a gradual change since
我们将逐步进行改变，因为
the progress difference is
进度差异是
making a gradual change.
逐渐变化。
If we take a closer look
如果我们仔细观察
in this stage in the middle,
在这个中间阶段，
you'll find out that not only will
你会发现不仅会
C1 see a gradual round-trip delay increase,
C1看到了逐渐增加的往返延迟。
but since the otherwise solicited data
但由于其他方式获取的数据
will be used to satisfy C1's interests,
将被用来满足C1的利益需求，
C1's data arrival rate will show as
C1的数据到达率将显示为
C2's interest sending rate
C2的兴趣发送率
or C2's data arrival rate.
或C2的数据到达率。
Well meanwhile C1 being
嗯，与此同时C1正在
able trying to catch up,
正在努力追赶，
will send much faster than C2.
将会比C2发送得更快。
That means that C1,
这意味着C1，将会比C2发送得更快。
will also see a mismatch of
也将会看到不匹配的情况
its interest sending rate and
其利息发送率和
data arrival rate is
数据到达率是
sent faster than it received.
发送速度比接收速度快。
Both of these two,
这两个都是，
both delay and rate indicates
that there is a congestion,
that there is a congestion,
存在拥堵，
which is not true in this case, as we know.
这在这种情况下并不成立，正如我们所知。
People may ask, is this an issue
人们可能会问，这是一个问题吗？
because C1 is satisfied by
因为C1得到了满足
cache and cache is effectively used.
缓存得到了有效利用。
This bottleneck bandwidth is used by
这个瓶颈带宽被使用了。
this first starter and
这个首发和
is also effectively used.
也被有效利用。
Well, we need to look into this.
嗯，我们需要研究一下这个问题。
The issue is that let's
我们需要研究的问题是，让我们...
say I change the bottleneck link
说我改变了瓶颈环节
from the first starter to
从第一个发起者到
the forwarder with very low value.
转发者的价值非常低。
We know that C1 does not even use this link.
我们知道C1甚至都不使用这个链接。
When this happens, the
当发生这种情况时，
false congestion is still there.
虚假拥堵依然存在。
So whenever C1 is
~!@#$%^&*()
trying to catch up with the first starter,
试图追上第一个出发者，
it will always detect
它将始终检测到
a congestion and give up its bandwidth.
它将放弃其带宽并造成拥堵。
Because of this,
因此，
the C2's bottleneck link
C2的瓶颈环节
produced to the forwarder which
交给货运代理的那部分
is not even used by C1,
没有被C1使用，
there'll be a rate-limiting factor
将会有一个限速因素
of C1's performance and
的C1性能表现以及
also the bottleneck link
也是瓶颈环节
is not effectively used in this case.
没有在这种情况下得到有效利用。
So I think this is an interesting issue that
所以我认为这是一个有趣的问题，它
illustrates that our initial design
说明我们最初的设计
does not match the requirement of,
不符合要求的，
we need to be tolerant
我们需要宽容。
who run through time variations.
穿越时光变迁的人。
We also think that
我们也认为
this issue may show up with
这个问题可能会出现在
other congestion control algorithms
其他拥塞控制算法
that rely on minimum
依赖于最小的
round-trip delay measurements,
往返时延测量，
such as TCPB Vegas or PBR.
例如TCP Vegas或PBR。
We find that there are
我们发现有
true potential ways to address this issue.
解决这个问题的真正潜在方法。
The first one is on the consumer side,
消费者方面是第一个问题，
if the consumer will do reordering of
如果消费者将会重新排序
its segment requests holders
它的段请求持有者
whenever it sees a round trip time increase.
每当它看到往返时间增加时。
For example, when C1
例如，当C1
sees a round trip time increase,
看到往返时间增加，
it will reorder is segment request holder and
它将重新排序它的段请求持有者和
C2 will now do the same thing
C2现在将做同样的事情。
because C1 and C2 as at hand,
因为C1和C2就在手边，
we will have a different
我们将会有一个不同的
interest sending holder.
利息发放持有人。
So if C1 is satisfied by data
因此，如果C1通过数据得到满足
solicited by the other consumer,
被其他消费者请求，
it will be able to
它将能够
increase data reordering or round
增加数据重排序或循环
trip time sample jittering that
增加行程时间样本的抖动，以便在中间阶段实现其转折。
will hinge that its in the middle stage.
将会取决于它是否在中间阶段。
Another way is to ask forwarders for help.
另一种方式是请求货运代理提供帮助。
If forwarders can provide
如果货运代理能够提供
information about whether queue has built up,
消费者也可以了解是否积累了排队。
the consumer can also understand that,
消费者也可以了解这一点，
while it's round trip delay
其往返延迟时间
it observes is increasing,
它观察到的正在增加，
it does not necessarily mean
它并不一定意味着
a congestion and don't give
它并不一定意味着拥堵并且不会在那些情况下增加带宽。
up bandwidth in those cases.
在那些情况下增加带宽。
As for the next step of our work,
关于我们工作的下一步，
and we hope to explore
我们希望探索
some non-cubic methods to
探索一些非立方体的方法来
control interests sending,
控制利益发送，
and also continue our study on
并且继续我们的研究工作
the algorithm behavior and
算法行为和
the caching and multipath forwarding.
缓存和多路径转发。
Lastly, we hope to explore
最后，我们希望探索
some potential forwarder feedbacks
一些潜在的货代反馈
that benefits performance or
提升性能的好处或者
the design of
设计
the congestion control algorithm.
拥塞控制算法。
That's all for my talk today.
这就是我今天的演讲内容。
Thanks a lot and we'll have any questions.
非常感谢，如果有任何问题，我们会提出来。
>> Thanks Sicheng, we're
非常感谢，Sicheng，我们正在
running out of time.
我们正在快要没时间了。
There are a number of questions on
我们有很多问题需要讨论。
this lecture and on people are reacting.
这场演讲的内容和人们的反应。
One quick one, this is end-to-end right?
是的，这是端到端的。
The intermediate nodes are not involved.
中间节点没有参与。
>> Yes, yes. That's a great question.
是的，是的。这是一个很好的问题。
So we hope to start by end-to-end,
所以我们希望从端到端开始，
first because it's simple and also,
首先因为它简单，而且，
we hope to have a good understanding of what
我们希望能够很好地理解什么
are those things end consumers can
那些是最终消费者可以~!@#$%^&*()
do and what are the things missing.
需要做的事情以及缺失的东西。
So later we could move to
所以稍后我们可以移动到
a better design while having more parties,
一个更好的设计同时涉及更多的参与方，
especially the forwarders involved.
尤其是涉及到的货运代理。
>> Please, go ahead on the Slack channel,
请继续在Slack频道上进行。
answer a few interesting questions
回答一些有趣的问题
on measurement interval,
在测量间隔期间，
taking into account
考虑到
the queue congestion and so on.
队列拥堵等问题。
For the sake of time, we're
为了节省时间，我们将
moving to the next speaker.
为了节省时间，我们将移交给下一位发言人。Thank you again Sichen.
Thank you again Sichen.
再次感谢思辰。
Next speaker is Junxiao Shi.
下一位发言人是石俊霄。
He is a researcher at NIST,
他是美国国家标准与技术研究院的一名研究员，
and he's a core NDN developer,
他是核心NDN开发者，
and has been developing
他一直在开发
NDN network forward there since 2013.
NDN网络自2013年以来一直在那里进行转发。
He is going to talk about The
他将要谈论的是The~!@#$%^&*()
NDN-DPDK file server that he
他将要谈论的是NDN-DPDK文件服务器，它是为了支持
developed in support of
发展以支持
this project. Go ahead.
这个项目。继续。
>> As you said it's Junxiao
>> 正如你所说，那是俊晓。
and I'm talking about
我正在谈论的是
NDN-DPDK File Server
NDN-DPDK文件服务器
for Data-Intensive Science Applications.
适用于数据密集型科学应用。
NDN-DPDK started
NDN-DPDK启动了
as a high-speed NDN forwarder,
作为一个高速NDN转发器，
and we achieved 100 gigabytes per
我们实现了每秒100吉字节的传输速度，
seconds in the ICN Standard paper by
在ICN标准文件中的秒内
adopting vital algorithm and reducing
采用关键算法并减少
overhead through the use
通过使用减少开销
of the Data Plane Development Kit.
的数据平面开发工具包。
Today's focus is on the file server
今天的重点是文件服务器。
we newly developed this year.
我们今年新开发的。
The motivation of doing
我们今年新开发的这个文件服务是因为我们已经有了做这件事的动机。
this file service is because we already have
我们开发这个文件服务是因为我们已经有了...
a high-speed of forwarder and it
与快速应用程序很搭配。
Data-intensive science they use
他们使用的是数据密集型科学。
them in big data or mainly large files.
他们主要处理大数据或大型文件。
In the case of the Large Hadron Collider,
在大型强子对撞机的情况下，
it will operate a Terabytes of data every
它每天将处理数太字节的数据。
day and there is
每天都有
already existing
已经存在
IP-based replication system,
基于IP的复制系统，
and also IP-based client,
以及基于IP的客户端，
and so we cannot change overnight.
因此，我们无法一夜之间改变。
A common way of doing
一种常见的做法是
NDN file server is using
NDN文件服务器正在使用中
the repo such as
~!@#$%^&*()
the NDN python repo mentioned earlier today.
提到的NDN Python仓库在今天早些时候。
But the drawback of the repo
但该仓库的缺点在于，
is when we insert a file to the repo,
是当我们向仓库中插入一个文件时，
it need to correct the files into
它需要将文件纠正为
data packets during the insertion,
在插入过程中的数据包，
which double the storage demand
使存储需求翻倍
and there are Terabytes of data.
并且有数以太字节的数据。
This is not feasible in the case of index.
这在索引的情况下是不可行的。
The NDN-DPDK file server
NDN-DPDK文件服务器
it works differently.
它的工作方式不同。
It can read from the existing storage and
它可以从现有存储中读取数据并且
then create a data package on
然后在上面创建一个数据包
the fly weights being requested,
请求的飞行重量，
so it does not use more storage.
因此它不会使用更多的存储空间。
As a protocol, file server has two steps,
作为一种协议，文件服务器有两个步骤，
the first step is to retrieve the metadata.
第一步是检索元数据。
The metadata contains a version NDN prefix
元数据包含一个版本NDN前缀。
to fetch this particular version
获取这个特定版本
of the file,
的文件，
and it contains the file size and timestamps.
并且它包含了文件大小和时间戳。
It is extension of
它是的扩展
the real time data retrieval protocol.
实时数据检索协议。
The second step is referred to as
第二步被称为
a file content segment
一个文件内容片段
by segment, currently,
按照段落来说，目前，
it does not support
它不支持
equation sign because it's
方程式符号因为它的~!@#$%^&*()
not needed in the use case,
在使用场景中不需要，
but we can possibly add this if
但如果有必要的话，我们可以考虑添加这个功能。
we have hardware crypto accelerator.
我们有硬件加密加速器。
Of course, when you factor this,
当然，当你考虑这个因素时，
you can use a condition control
你可以使用条件控制。
mentioned in a previous talk.
在之前的谈话中提到过。
That is a way as a file server,
这是作为文件服务器的一种方式，
access to the underlying storage
访问底层存储
is using the io_uring.
正在使用 io_uring。
a new asynchronous I/O API for Linux.
一种用于Linux的新异步I/O API。
It is available since the Linux kernel
它自Linux内核起就可用。
5.2 and is enhanced in later kernel version.
5.2版本中可用，并在后续的内核版本中得到增强。
The benefit of io_uring is,
io_uring的好处是，
it request through our system
它通过我们的系统发出请求。
costs [NOISE] and using read or aio_read.
成本 [噪声] 以及使用 read 或 aio_read。
The way it works is applications
应用程序的工作方式
such as NDN-DPDK file server,
例如NDN-DPDK文件服务器，
it prepare a reader request which contains
它准备了一个包含读取请求的内容，
that file descriptor, a destination buffer,
该文件描述符、一个目标缓冲区，
and as a byte offset that it's
和作为字节偏移量，它是
submitted to the kernels
提交到内核
The submission does not require system cost,
提交不需要系统成本，
[NOISE] and the kernel will process
和内核将会处理
this request and when it's
这个请求，当它的
complete it comes back to
完成后它又回来了
in another completion kill,
在另一个完成后的终结中，
which is a fellow process
这是一个相关的过程。
were cooled a process
此为一个冷却过程。
further such as sending a data package.
进一步比如发送一个数据包。
[NOISE] With that,
~!@#$%^&*()
this diagram is an
这张图是一个
architectural of a file server.
这张图是一个文件服务器的架构。
A file server connect to
一台文件服务器连接到
a local NDN-DPDK forwarder
一个本地NDN-DPDK转发器
so I shared the Memory
所以我共享了内存
Packet Interface,memif,
数据包接口，内存接口，
does the same work as NDRC library does.
与国家发展和改革委员会图书馆的工作相同。
Then, the input test read can perform
Then, the input test can be performed
low dependency between
低依赖性
several producer threads.
几个生产者线程。
Within our producer thread
在我们的生产者线程内
incoming interests is
即将到来的利益是
classified [NOISE] as is
分类为原样[噪音]
a metadata interests or segment interests.
对元数据感兴趣或对段落感兴趣。
For metadata interests, it has had a fire
对元数据感兴趣，它已经引起了极大的关注。
right away with metadata, data packet.
立即处理元数据，数据包。
For segment interests it is
针对细分市场的兴趣来说，它是
converted to a reader request,
转换为读者请求，
and then sent into io_uring into the kernel.
然后发送到内核中的io_uring。
When the io_ reader requests complete,
当io_reader请求完成后，
it comes back to the producer as red,
它以红色的形式返回给生产者，
and then it becomes
然后它变成了
a segment data which
段数据，它~!@#$%^&*()
is sent to the output thread.
被发送到输出线程。
[NOISE] We use
我们使用
this open file descriptor table
这个打开的文件描述符表
in issue producers thread.
在问题生产者线程中。
The purpose of this data
这个数据的目的是为了在问题生产者线程中重用结构。
structure is to reuse
结构是为了重用
a file descriptor for
一个用于
interests accessing the same file.
访问同一个文件的兴趣。
It contains a hash table of
它包含了一个哈希表，
file descriptors indexed by a filename,
它通过文件名索引文件描述符，
so that we don't need to
因此我们就不需要
open the same file multiple times.
所以我们就不需要多次打开同一个文件。
When a file is no longer being
当一个文件不再被
used up by ongoing reader request,
正在进行的读取请求不再使用时，
it will go into
它将进入
the clean-up queue and eventually closed.
它将进入清理队列并最终关闭。
[NOISE] We did some preliminary benchmark
我们进行了一些初步的基准测试。
using two physical machines.
使用了两台物理机。
We ran the forward and
我们运行了前向和~!@#$%^&*()
a file server on the physical machines.
我们在物理机上运行了一个文件服务器。
The underlying storage is MBME,
底层存储使用的是MBME，
and that's over a 100
而且那超过了100
gigabits per second of the linker,
千兆位每秒的链路，
the other machine runs
另一台机器运行
condition-aware fetcher,
条件感知抓取器，
which implements
实现了
CUBIC-like condition control algorithm
立方体状的条件控制算法
that we tried to transfer
我们尝试传输
a single file of 20 gigabits
一个20千兆比特的单个文件
over certain topology within the issues.
在特定拓扑结构中解决这些问题。
We try this for different segments sizes,
我们尝试了不同的段落大小，
and a five trials each.
我们进行了五次试验。
As we can see, if we use
我们可以看到，如果我们使用
a larger segment size that
一个更大的段大小，那
we can get to better good input,
我们可以得到更好的输入，
for the larger segment size
为了更大的段大小
of eight kilobytes,
为了更大的段大小，八千字节，我们在这个单元得到了这个好的输入，
we get this good input in this unit,
我们在这个单元得到了这个好的输入，
which is 1800 megabytes per second,
我们在这个单元得到了这个好的输入，它是每秒1800兆字节，and this is roughly 60 percent of
and this is roughly 60 percent of
这大约是理论最大值的60%
the theoretical maximum
理论最大值
sequential reads speedup
顺序读取加速
of this particular MVM device
of this particular MVM device -> 特定的这款MVM设备上
on the file server side.
在文件服务器端。
Of course, NDN-DPDK also has a forwarder,
当然，NDN-DPDK也有一个转发器，
and we keep Improving the forwarder.
我们持续改进转发器。
Way important improvement we did this year,
我们今年做出的重要改进是，
is to relieve the input of bottleneck.
是为了缓解输入的瓶颈。
Because in our IC and 20th paper input as
因为在我们的IC和第20篇论文中输入为
thread was identified as
线程被识别为
a bottleneck of the forwarder.
转发器的瓶颈。
Now we can use the multiple input
现在我们可以使用多重输入。
as threads forwarder,
作为线程转发器，
but this functionality is
但这个功能是
subject to hideaway and
受限于隐居和
their travel limitations,
他们的旅行限制，
because it's a current hideaway
因为这是一个当前的藏身之处
they only understand IP.
他们只懂IP。
This whole file, we only got it working for
这整个文件，我们只让它成功运行了
VXLAN transport on the Mellanox ConnectX-5
Mellanox ConnectX-5上的VXLAN传输
, is an adapter.
是一种适配器。
The way it works is when
它的工作原理是当
a packet comes to the hardware,
一个数据包到达硬件时，
we have a sequence of
我们有一个序列
received scaling ISS rules.
收到了调整国际空间站规则的通知。
Those rules, they were mentioned
那些规则，他们提到过。
source IP address and
源 IP 地址和
destination port to be the VXLAN port.
目的端口设置为VXLAN端口。
Then, the hardware
接着，硬件
while computing the hash of
在计算哈希值时
UDP 5-tuple, since EBX lens,
UDP 5元组，自EBX镜头起，
a UDP source port,
UDP源端口，
is a random numbers,
是一个随机数，
this means, every packet
这意味着，每个数据包
could have different hash values.
可能会有不同的哈希值。
We can say a Hardware will pick up kills
我们可以说硬件会捡起杀戮。
based on the hash value using
根据哈希值使用
the last bit of the hash value,
根据哈希值的最后一部分，
so if we have two kills,
所以如果我们有两个击杀，
it can't go can go to both input as threads.
它不能同时进入两个输入作为线程。
This effective reliefs
这有效缓解了
the input of bottleneck.
这有效缓解了瓶颈的输入。
Of course, the next talk is
当然，接下来的演讲是
about FPGA Acceleration,
关于FPGA加速，
would it replace all
它会替换所有吗？
these and a part of the input thread.
这些以及输入线程的一部分。
To measure the effectives,
为了衡量效果，
we need a benchmark,
我们需要一个基准，
and to simplify benchmark,
为了简化基准，
we created an
我们创建了一个
interactive benchmark web application
我们创建了一个交互式基准测试Web应用程序，
that is part of an NDN-DPDK codebase.
它是NDN-DPDK代码库的一部分。
If you have a topology
如果你有一个拓扑图
like this and then you can enter
像这样，然后你可以输入
some parameter and the system will
一些参数然后系统会
automate it to a benchmark
将其自动化为一个基准
for you and show it as a results.
为您展示并作为结果呈现。
What you need after two-way,
您在双向之后所需要的是，
we did a benchmark of see
我们做了一个基准测试来看看~!@#$%^&*()
how effective we relieve
我们如何有效地缓解
the input of bottleneck.
瓶颈的输入。
Orange part is when we have
橙色部分是当我们有
only one input thread and
只有一个输入线程和
blue part is two input thread.
蓝色部分是两个输入线程。
As a leak, I see If we
~!@#$%^&*()
only have one input thread,
只有一个输入线程，
it's a input thread becomes a bottleneck,
输入线程成为了瓶颈，
and when we have six, four threads,
当我们有六个，四个线程时，
and its speed is a 109 gigabits per second,
它的速度是每秒109吉比特。
but when we have two inputs thread,
但是当我们有两个输入线程时，
we got to 134 gigabits
我们达到了134千兆比特
per second but that's the speed.
我们达到了134千兆比特每秒，但这就是速度。如果我们有更多的转发线程 We've reached 134 terabits per second, but that's the speed. If we have even more forwarding threads
If we have even more forwarding thread
如果我们有更多的转发线程
as a speeder is going down,
随着超速者减速，
[NOISE] so I suppose there's
~!@#$%^&*()
some memory and bandwidth limitations,
一些内存和带宽限制，
and we all keep digging at this area.
我们都在不断深入挖掘这个领域。
Apart from that, we also tried to
此外，我们还尝试了
reduce CPU utilization when
降低CPU使用率时
forward is not a processing traffic.
转发不是处理流量。
As measuring the YaNFD paper,
在测量YaNFD论文时，
NDN-DPDK is using a 100 percent CPU polling,
NDN-DPDK使用的是100% CPU轮询，
so polling is fundamentally how
所以轮询是基本的工作方式，
DPDK works, I cannot change that,
DPDK的工作方式是固定的，我无法改变这一点，
but it doesn't have to
但这并非必须的。
use a 100 percent CPU,
使用100%的CPU资源，
so we introduced
所以我们引入了
a new threadsleep compile-time option.
因此我们引入了一个新的编译时选项：threadsleep。
If a thread process 0 packets in a pool,
如果一个线程在池中处理了0个数据包，
it was sleep or for one nanosecond,
它是睡眠状态，哪怕只有一纳秒，
and if I add only continuous,
如果我仅仅添加持续性，
we gradually increases sleep duration.
我们逐渐增加睡眠时间。
As we can see, if we have
我们可以看到，如果我们有~!@#$%^&*()
a threadedsleep option [inaudible].
一个带有线程睡眠选项的[听不清]。
Using set benchmark to
使用设置基准来
only reduce them slightly.
仅稍微减少它们。
But when it's not processing
但当它不在处理时
any traffic without sleeping,
任何不休眠的流量，
it will use 14 CPU costs,
它将消耗14个CPU成本，
and when it's sleeping it only use
它在休眠状态下只会使用
half CPU cost when added together.
在加起来时只会使用一半的CPU成本。
The NDN-DPDK codebase is
NDN-DPDK 代码库是
open source on github,
在 GitHub 上开源，
and this year as you can see
今年如你所见
what I did to the file server,
我对文件服务器所做的操作，
as the interactive benchmark,
作为交互式的基准，
and also improve
也可以改善
the user documentation so you
用户文档，所以你可以按照那份文档
can follow that documentation
可以按照那份文档进行操作
that it installed that data started.
可以按照那份文档进行操作，数据开始安装了。We also expanded the platform support.
We also expanded the platform support
我们还扩大了平台支持。
always supported the DB11 PVM.
我们一直支持DB11 PVM。
We now allow using IP and the idea are the
我们现在允许使用IP，其思想是
same as an adaptor usings the AFXDP driver.
与使用AFXDP驱动程序的适配器相同。
We also supported PLUDP
我们也支持了PLUDP。
and a VX Nintendo transport.
我们还增加了对VX Nintendo传输的支持。
We also added a support for container net and
我们还增加了对容器网络的支持。
a file for file experimental platforms.
一个用于文件实验平台的文件。
[NOISE] Thank you.
谢谢。
>> Thank you, Junxiao,
>> 谢谢，俊霄，
we are only five minutes
我们只剩下五分钟了。
left in this session,
在这个环节中，我们只剩下
so we're not taking questions we'll move to
所以我们不接受提问，我们将继续进行
the next talk by Michael Lo.
下一个演讲由Michael Lo进行。
Michael, we'll give you
我们将给予你Michael
ten minutes will be to wait
等待将是十分钟。
five minutes from the next session, I guess.
距离下一个环节大概还有五分钟。
You can go ahead and start sharing screen.
您可以开始共享屏幕了。
>> Can you see the screen?
>> 你能看到屏幕吗？
>> Michael? Sorry.
>> 迈克尔？对不起。
>> Sorry, you [inaudible] [OVERLAPPING].
>> 对不起，你[听不清][重叠的声音]。
>> Go ahead and start sharing,
>> 继续开始分享吧，
while I introduce you.
在我介绍你的时候继续开始分享吧，Michael Lo, 是
Michael Lo, is
迈克尔·罗，是
a graduate student at UCLA working
迈克尔·罗，是一名在加州大学洛杉矶分校（UCLA）攻读研究生的学生，与教授Jason Cong合作
with Professor Jason Cong In
与教授Jason Cong在
the center for domain specific computing.
领域特定计算中心。
He's going to talk
他将要讲话
about the FPGA acceleration
关于FPGA加速
for the NDN forward
关于NDN转发
or the Junxiao Chan just talked about.
或者刚才陈俊霄提到的。
Go ahead Michael.
请继续，迈克尔。
>> Can you see the screen?
>> 你能看到屏幕吗？
>> Not yet.
>> 还没有。
>> I could see it.
>> 我能看到它。
>> Yeah. How about now?
>> 是的。现在怎么样？
>> I'll be talking about our progress on
>> 我将讨论我们在进展上的情况
the FPGA-based acceleration
基于FPGA的加速
for the forwarding pipeline.
用于转发管道。
As a quick background, we all
作为一个快速的背景介绍，我们所有人
know how NDN work.
作为一个快速的背景介绍，我们所有人都了解NDN是如何工作的。如果一个节点正在寻找特定的数据，
If a node is looking for a specific data,
如果一个节点正在寻找特定的数据，
it doesn't have to go to the producer
它不必去找生产者。
to retrieve that data
已经有了那些数据
if its next near node already
如果它的下一个近邻节点已经
has it compared to IP-based where you have to
与基于IP的系统相比，你必须要
forward your request to
转发你的请求到
the destination specified.
指定的目的地。
With NDN you don't have to do that.
使用NDN，你无需这样做。
Here's a quick breakdown
这是一个快速的概述
of the forwarding pipeline.
的转发管道。
Let's say if we're looking for a request
的转发管道 for /a/b,
for /a/b,
的转发管道为/a/b，
and if it's in next neighbors node,
如果它位于相邻的节点中，
then you can simply just grab
那么你可以简单地抓住
the data that's in the back cover.
数据就在封底里。
If that data doesn't exist,
如果那些数据不存在，
you have to go through
你必须经过
the entire forwarding logic.
整个转发逻辑。
You have to insert into
你必须插入到
a pending interest table
待处理的利息表
and then you have to go
然后你必须去
through the routing table and figure out
通过路由表并找出
what's the next node it's sending to.
它将发送到的下一个节点是什么。
One problem with
它将发送到的下一个节点是什么。One problem with the NDN architecture is that we
the NDN architecture is that we
在NDN架构中，我们
notice that it uses
注意到它使用了
hierarchical names instead
它使用了层次化名称而不是固定的32位或者128位地址。
of fixed 32 or even 128 bit address.
它使用分层的命名方式，而不是固定的32位或者128位地址。
That's the one that is also a benefit of NDN.
这也是NDN的一个优势。
You can have variable name lengths
您可以使用不同长度的变量名。
to represent your data, they're not fixed.
为了表示您的数据，它们不是固定的。
This is great for the upstream user.
这对上游用户来说很棒。
They can specify whatever they want.
他们可以随意指定他们想要的。
However, we need to process it,
然而，我们需要处理它，
we need some way to
我们需要找到某种方法来
transform it into a unique or
将其转化为一个独一无二的或者
a fixed length identifier so
将其转化为一个独一无二的固定长度的标识符，以便
that the processing is much more easier.
使得处理过程变得更加容易。
There are two criteria that have to be met.
需要满足两个标准。
Each prefix needs to have
每个前缀需要具有
a unique hash or a unique name.
一个独特的哈希或一个独特的名称。
If we want to represent it as
如果我们想将其表示为
a fixed number of bits,
一个固定数量的位，
then we use some hashing algorithm.
然后我们使用某种哈希算法。
In this case, it's a SIP hash.
在这种情况下，它是一个SIP哈希。
The SIP hash algorithm used by
在这种情况下，它是一个SIP哈希算法。
NDN is slightly different than
NDN与之稍有不同
the general SIP hash used.
NDN与之稍有不同，主要区别在于通常使用的SIP哈希。
The main difference for
NDN与之稍有不同，主要区别在于
the SIP hash used in the NDN is
NDN中使用的SIP哈希是
that every end of prefix,
每个前缀的末尾，
you have to go through
你必须经历
additional six rounds of
额外六轮的
these XOR and additional
这些异或和额外的
ADD and ROTATE operations
加法和旋转操作
to produce the 64 bit hash.
生成64位哈希。
I'll just go over a quick example.
我将简要说明一个例子。
Let's say for example, we have
我们举个例子，我们有
this /aaaaa/bbbbb/ccccc/ddddd.
这个/aaaaa/bbbbb/ccccc/ddddd。
First we traverse the string.
首先我们遍历字符串。
We see that slash a is one prefix.
我们看到斜杠a是一个前缀。
We have to do with six rounds of computation.
我们需要进行六轮计算。
The total number of
我们到目前为止完成的轮数是
six and we've produced one hash.
我们到目前为止完成的轮数是六，我们已经生成了一个哈希值。Now as we traverse even more,
Now as we traverse even more,
我们继续遍历下去，
we finally hit eight bytes.
我们最终达到了八字节。
We have to do a two round computation.
我们需要进行两轮计算。
We have done eight rounds so
我们已经进行了八轮计算。
far and we still only produced one hash.
我们已经进行了八轮计算。正如你所看到的，到目前为止我们仍然只生成了一个哈希值。
traverse through the entire string,
遍历整个字符串，
we need to do 30 rounds of computation just
我们需要进行30轮计算才能
for a name of 25 characters.
我们需要进行30轮计算才能得到一个25个字符的名字。
As you can see, this can get
正如你所见，这可能会变得
computationally more complex depending
在你所输入的名称上，这可能会变得在计算上更为复杂，取决于
on your input name,
在你所输入的名称上，
especially if you have a lot of
尤其是如果你有很多
prefixes in your name and they're short.
尤其是如果你有很多前缀在你的名字里，并且它们是简短的。总结一下，我们已经做了30轮。
Just to summarize, we've done 30 rounds
总结一下，我们已经做了30轮
of computation for
了计算工作。
a 25-character input and we
完成了计算工作。一个25字符的输入，我们只产生了四个哈希。
only produced four hashes.
我们只产生了四个哈希。
The next step is to
在调度表中查找
where your dispatch to
在你的调度表中查找
the thread now handle this input.
线程现在处理这个输入。
A lot of downside of using a dispatch table
使用调度表的许多缺点
is you need to try
你需要尝试去弄清楚如何
to figure out how
去弄清楚如何
big your table size should be,
去弄清楚桌子有多大，
otherwise you're running to issues.
否则你会遇到问题。
need a specified prefix depth.
需要一个指定的前缀深度。
Then depending on your table size,
那么根据你的表格大小，
you use the last n-bits of
你使用最后的n位
the hash to index into that table.
将哈希用于索引那个表。
As stated, this can lead
这可能会导致
to some issues with bouncing your tables.
这可能会导致一些关于弹跳你的表格的问题。
One problem is if you have
一个问题是如果你有太大的表格，
too large of a table,
如果你的表格太大，
then you have really poor
那么你的确很差劲
locality during lookup
在查找期间的位置性
because one hash may be
因为一个哈希值可能会
in cache and then the next hash
映射到同一个索引上，因此下一个哈希值进来时，可能不在缓存中。
that comes in may not be in cache.
可能不在缓存中。
You got to evict
你得驱逐~!@#$%^&*()
the entries and bringing it in.
条目的输入和引入。
Then maybe another hash comes in and
然后可能又有另一个哈希值传入，
you fix the previous entry, so on like that.
你修正了前一个条目，就这样继续下去。
However, if you have a smaller table,
但是，如果你有一个较小的表格，
it can lead to imbalance thread workload.
它可能导致线程工作负载不平衡。
As an example here,
这里作为一个例子，
let's say we're using the last 16 bits
我们可以使用最后16位
to index the dispatch table.
来索引分派表。
The last 16 bits are all the same,
最后16位是完全相同的，
but the other 48 bits are not the same.
但是其他的48位并不相同。
But in this case, all these four hashes
但在这种情况下，这四个哈希值
will be dispatched to one thread.
将会被分配到一个线程中。
As you can see, if you
将会看到，如果你
use the last bits in this case,
使用这种情况下的最后一点。
it will be sensing two different threads.
它将会感应到两个不同的线程。
If you use the last 18,
如果你使用最后18个，
it would be sensing four different threads.
它将会感应到四个不同的线程。
But like I said,
但正如我所说，
as you use more bits,
随着你使用更多的位，
your table size will increase.
你的表格大小将会增加。
For our design exploration on the FPGA,
在我们对FPGA进行的设计探索中，
our goal is to try to identify
我们的目标是尝试识别
any overlaps in computation
任何在计算中的重叠
as much as possible.
尽可能地。
For the SIP hash algorithm,
对于SIP散列算法，
there are some computational overlaps.
在计算上有一些重叠。
Then for the dispatch level,
那么对于调度层来说，
we can actually do it while
我们实际上可以在此时进行它
the hashing is still being computed.
哈希计算仍在进行中。
But it really depends on the depth
但这确实取决于深度。
specified to see if
指定查看是否
we can actually hide these overlaps.
我们实际上可以隐藏这些重叠部分。
One advantage for that FPGA
FPGA在这种情况下的一个优势是
over the CPU in this case is that
FPGA在这种情况下相对于CPU的一个优势是，
because these compositional overlaps
因为这些组合重叠
or these parallel lookups,
对于这些并行查找，
they are relatively fast
它们相对来说很快。
task and they're short.
任务而且它们很短。
It's not really worth it
它真的不值得
to spawn a CPU thread just to do it.
为此单独生成一个CPU线程是不值得的。
Essentially you're just incurring
本质上你只是在引发
the CPU spawning thread overhead.
你只是在触发CPU产生线程开销。
But with the FPGA design,
但是使用FPGA设计，
you don't have this issue at all,
你根本就不会遇到这个问题，
you simply have this
你根本就有这个
RE baked into your design.
RE 已经嵌入到你的设计中了。
Where's the SIP hash computation overlap?
SIP哈希计算的重叠在哪里？
In the NDN.
在NDN中。
Every time you need an end of prefix,
每次你需要一个前缀的结尾，
you have to do a final six round computation,
你必须进行最后六轮的计算，
and this actually doesn't
这实际上并不会
affect the next prefix at all.
影响下一个前缀。
For example, in this case,
例如，在这种情况下，
I'm computing the prefix
我正在计算前缀
of /aa in onetime step.
的/aa在一次时间步中。
I need to compute
I need to compute ~!@#$%^&*()
the final six rounds and a prefix of /aa.
最后六轮和一个前缀 /aa。
But at the same time, I can also start
但同时，我也可以开始
computing the prefix of /bbbb.
计算/bbbb的前缀。
We already have some competition
我们已经有了一些竞争。
over last one, bring these hashes.
在最后一个之后，带上这些哈希值。
Another thing is during lookup is that let's
在查找过程中还有一点是让我们
say we specified at depth equal 2,
如果我们指定深度等于2，
we actually just need the hash at
我们实际上只需要哈希值在
/bbbb to be sent to
/bbbb 需要被发送到
the lookup table while the rest of
查找表中的其余部分
the hashes are still being computed.
哈希值仍在计算中。
However, there isn't really much benefit if,
然而，如果情况并非如此，实际上并没有太多好处，
for example, let's say your depth is
例如，假设你的深度是
specified greater than
指定的更大于
the number of prefixes on the name.
名称上的前缀数量。
For example, let's say
例如，我们假设
my depth is equal to 5,
我的深度等于5，
then we won't really see any benefits of
那么我们实际上不会真正看到任何好处
these lookup overlapping parallel
这些查找重叠并行
hash reputation because I
hash reputation because I 必须等到名字的结尾才会
have to wait until the end of the name is
必须等到名字的结尾才会
computed before I can send it
在我可以发送它之前必须先计算出来
to the naming dispatch table.
到命名分派表。
Also in our design,
我们的设计中也是如此，
we implemented a custom cache.
我们实现了一个自定义缓存。
Instead of evicting, let's say,
我们不是要驱逐，比如说，
a 64-bit line like in CPU,
一条像在CPU中的64位线路，
we actually just store
我们实际上只是存储
the index of those recently hit.
我们实际上只是存储那些最近被访问的索引。Here's the overall architectural design.
Here's the overall architectural design
这是整体的架构设计。
on the FPGA is very simple.
在FPGA上非常简单。
We have two kernels.
我们有两个内核。
One that specifically does the hashing,
一个专门负责哈希运算的内核。
another one that
另一个专门负责查找的内核。
specifically does the lookup.
专门负责查找。
Essentially the CPU is sending
本质上CPU正在发送
named input to the hashing kernel first.
命名输入首先传递给哈希内核。
Inside our hashing kernels,
在我们的哈希内核中，
we can handle up to date
我们可以处理最新的数据。
named strings in parallel.
并行处理命名字符串。
The lookup kernel, they only handle
查找内核，它们只处理
one input lookup at a time
一次只查找一个输入
where it uses a multiplexer to go in
它使用一个多路复用器进行输入
a round robin fashion
采用循环轮询的方式
to look up requests
来查找请求
from each processing element
来自每个处理单元
from the cache-in kernel.
来自缓存内核。
Here's our testing results or methodology.
这是我们的测试结果或方法论。
It's a standalone comparison.
这是一个独立的比较。
We've only compared the hashing computation
我们只比较了哈希计算
against our CPU and a lookup
相比于我们的CPU和查找
done on the CPU is not done
与我们的CPU和查找相比，完成的工作并没有完成
in an end-to-end where we
在一个端到端的过程中，我们
integrate it into a forwarder.
将其集成到转发器中。
We haven't done that step yet,
我们还没有执行那一步。
but we'll try to do that in the future.
但我们将来会尝试去做那一步。
Here's our CPU that
我们的CPU在这里。
we use it to compare against.
我们用它来进行比较。
As you can see, it has quite a small L1,
我们可以看到，它有一个相当小的L1缓存，
but relatively large L2 and L3 cache.
但相对较大的L2和L3缓存。
>> Yeah. Here,
是的，在这里。
we compare against one thread
我们将其与一个线程进行比较。
versus one processing element.
与一个处理单元相比较。
On the horizontal axis,
在水平轴上，
it's the number of
它是数量
bits used in the lookup table,
在查找表中使用的位数，
and then on the vertical axis is
然后在垂直轴上是
the depth specify for lookup,
查询时指定的深度，
and in the blue is
和在蓝色中是
the time it takes for CPU,
CPU所需的时间是，
and the gold is the time for FPGA.
和黄金一样，FPGA所需的时间是。
As you can see, as you go along
正如你所看到的，随着你的进行，
the vertical axis,
垂直轴，
the CPUs, you can start to see that
你可以开始看到CPU的情况，
the caching on the
缓存在
CPU really starts to be effective.
CPU真的开始发挥效果了。
Going from from depth of two to depth of 32,
从深度为2增加到深度为32，
you're really just having
你其实只是在
just cache thrashing around.
你其实只是在乱缓存。
As for FPGA, we
你其实只是在乱缓存，至于FPGA，我们并没有真正看到那个问题在哪里。
don't really see that problem at
我们并没有真正看到那个问题在哪里。
all because they are hidden away.
因为它们都被隐藏起来了。
Yeah, and then we do a comparison
是的，然后我们进行比较。
of up to eight processing elements.
高达八个处理单元。
One thing we noticed that is for
我们注意到的一点是对于
the fourth processing elements
第四个处理元素
on the FPGA and
在FPGA上并且
a processing element on FPGA,
在FPGA上的一个处理单元，
we don't see any further improvements.
我们没有看到任何进一步的改进。
We believe this is
我们认为这是
some communication overhead
一些通信开销
between the CPU and FPGA.
在CPU和FPGA之间。
As a part of future work,
作为未来工作的一部分，
one thing I didn't really mentioned
有一件事我之前没有真正提到过
is that the FPGA
那是FPGA吗？
actually requires
实际上需要
batching of your name inputs.
批处理您的名字输入。
So essentially, we can't do
所以本质上，我们不能做
any real time computation right now.
任何实时计算。
Let's say if you have
假设如果你有
packet arriving every microsecond,
数据包每微秒到达一次，
the FPGA expects that you
FPGA期望你~!@#$%^&*()
batch up to like for example,
批量处理，比如说，
in our design of [inaudible]
~!@#$%^&*()
at least 32 packets at
至少32个数据包在
a time before it can
在它能够之前至少需要一段时间
process it and like I said again,
在它能够处理它之前至少需要一段时间，就像我之前说的，
this is to reduce
这是为了减少
communication overhead between
通信开销在
CPU and FPGA and of course,
CPU和FPGA当然，
this will be feasible in online environment
这在在线环境中是可行的。
as your latency will be really high.
由于你的延迟会非常高。
As part of our future work, we're
作为我们未来工作的一部分，我们正在
looking to instead of
寻求替代
having extra data copy
拥有额外的数据复制
being moved around from CPU to FPGA,
被从CPU移动到FPGA，
we're looking into just allocating
我们正在考虑仅仅分配
a physical memory space on
我们正在考虑仅仅分配一个物理内存空间在CPU侧面，FPGA上。
the CPU side where the FPGA
我们正在考虑仅仅分配一个物理内存空间在CPU侧面，FPGA上，可以直接访问它。
can directly access it.
可以直接访问它。
We also hope to support
我们也希望支持
Longest Prefix Matching.
最长前缀匹配。
Previous papers have been exploring
以前的论文一直在探索
longest prefix matching and how to
最长前缀匹配以及如何减少所需的查找次数
reduce the number of lookups required.
减少所需的查找次数。
We hope to incorporate
我们希望将这些设计集成进FPGA设计中，还有，
it is possible for NDN interest packets to
我们希望将这些设计集成进FPGA设计中，还有，NDN兴趣包可能会使用令牌而非命名输入。
be using tokens instead of named inputs.
可能会使用令牌而非命名输入。
This is for receiving data packets that
这是用于接收数据包的，
are requested and we hope to also
收到请求，我们也希望能够
support token based inputs and then finally,
收到请求，我们也希望能够支持基于令牌的输入，然后最终，
we hope to integrate all our work into
我们希望将我们所有的工作整合进入
the NDN DPDK repository.
我们希望将我们所有的工作整合进入NDN DPDK仓库。>> All right. Thank you very much.
>> All right. Thank you very much.
好的。非常感谢您。
There's some discussion on Slack.
Slack 上有一些讨论。
You can take a look
你可以看一看
and we move to the next session,
我们继续进入下一个环节，
which is named Tactical and Wireless,
它被命名为战术与无线，
and it's shared by Tamer Rafael.
它由塔梅尔·拉斐尔共享。
Tamer received his PhD
塔梅尔获得了他的博士学位
in Computer Engineering
在计算机工程领域
from Virginia Polytechnic Institute
来自弗吉尼亚理工学院
and he's currently a
他目前是一名
Principal Information Security Scientist
首席信息安全科学家
at Mitre Corporation.
在Mitre公司。
Tamer, go ahead please.
塔默，请开始。
>> Can you all hear me?
>> 你们都能听见我说话吗？
>> Yes.
>> 是的。
>> Okay, great. Thank you. This session,
>> 好的，太好了。谢谢你。这个环节，
we have three talks.
我们有三场演讲。
The first talk is going to be from DARPA.
第一场演讲将由DARPA进行。
DARPA Secure Handhelds on
安全移动终端上的DARPA
Assured Resilient Networks at
安全可靠的网络在
the Tactical Edge SHARE.
安全可靠的网络在战术边缘分享。The talk is going to be given
The talk is going to be given
这场演讲即将由
by Dr. Mary Schurgot.
即将由Dr. Mary Schurgot加入。
Dr. Mary Schurgot joined
Dr. Mary Schurgot加入了
DARPA in March 2020 as
2020年3月加入了美国国防高级研究计划局（DARPA）担任
a Program Manager in
the Strategic Technology Office.
Strategic Technology Office.
战略技术办公室。
Her research interest includes
她的研究兴趣包括
secure and efficient data sharing,
安全高效的数据共享，
automated decision aids, and
自动化决策辅助工具，以及
the design of new networking
新型网络设计
innovation paradigms.
创新范式。
Before DARPA, Dr. Mary Schurgot was
在加入DARPA之前，玛丽·舒尔戈特博士是
the Practical Director
实践主任
of Machine Learning and
的机器学习与
Edge capability that CACI
的边缘计算能力，CACI
previously LGS Innovations,
之前是LGS Innovations，
where she developed and led
她在那里开发和领导了
programs at the intersection
她在那里开发和领导了位于分析、网络安全和网络交叉点的项目。
of analytics, cyber, and networking.
分析、网络安全和网络互联。
Dr. Schurgot, the floor is yours.
Dr. Schurgot，请发言。
>> Thanks, Tamer. Can you hear me
>> 谢谢，塔默。你能听到我说话吗？
and see my screen and see me?
能看到我的屏幕和我吗？
>> Yes, ma'am.
>> 是的，女士。
>> Thanks, Tamer. [LAUGHTER] Hi, everyone.
>> 谢谢你，塔默。[笑声] 大家好。
I'm very excited to be here again.
我很高兴再次来到这里。
Thank you for the invitation.
感谢您的邀请。
I'll try to get you some of your time back.
我会尽力为您节省一些时间。
You might be familiar with
您可能对此比较熟悉
the SHARE program and then I'll
分享计划，然后我会
talk about where we are with that and
讨论一下我们在这方面的进展情况，然后我会
then talk about them MINC program,
讨论一下MINC项目，
which is my new program.
这是我的新程序。
Again, I'm going quickly
我又要快速进行了。
through this because I know this
因为我知道这个，所以我得快速地处理这件事。
is a review for a lot of you.
这对你们很多人来说是一个复习。
The SHARE program started in 2016 timeframe,
SHARE项目始于2016年左右，
and the goal there was really to
实现的目标真的是为了
enable practical data sharing at
实现实际数据共享在
multiple security levels with a goal of
实现多个安全级别的目标是
enabling sharing between
实现共享之间
US forces and coalition partners.
美国军队及其联盟伙伴。
In contrast to how things are
与事情的现状相比
done today at the Tactical Edge,
在战术边缘完成的今天，
SHARE was trying to bring
SHARE正试图带来
Secure Enclave Technology and
安全飞地技术和
MINC data networking to
MINC数据网络连接至
the secure handheld or to a mobile phone.
安全手持设备或者移动电话。
What you're seeing on the bottom row
您在底部行看到的内容
there are the three main
这是三个主要的
components to SHARE,
这是三个主要的组成部分，用于分享，
the first being that
第一个是
we've shown that we can move
我们已经证明了我们可以移动
containerization software from
容器化软件从
the Cloud to handheld devices.
云端到手持设备。
Essentially, a secure
本质上是安全的
enclaves that are storing data of
存储数据的飞地
different sensitivity with levels
不同的敏感度等级
on a mobile device and
在移动设备上
then we incorporate that
然后我们将其整合进来
with MINC data networking,
与MINC数据网络一起，
where we're double encrypting
我们正在进行双重加密
the data packets and using
我们正在使用数据包并且利用NDN进行传输
NDN to transfer
利用NDN进行传输
those packets throughout the network,
在整个网络中传输这些数据包，
cache the data on
将数据缓存在
the end user devices
终端用户设备
and then the third focus area
然后第三个重点领域
has been all about
一直都是关于
configuration management and making
配置管理和制定
it easy for the war fighter to use SHARE.
便于战斗人员使用SHARE。
Again, for this crowd,
再一次，为了这个人群，
I don't really have to
我真的不需要
dwell on MINC data networking,
详细讨论MINC数据网络，
but I will on this slide point out that
但是在这张幻灯片上，我将指出
SHARE is integrated with
SHARE集成了
the Tactical Assault Kit.
战术突击工具包。
TAK is a common application that's
TAK是一个常用的应用程序，它是
used at the Tactical Edge.
用于战术边缘。
It's for exchanging command
它用于交换指挥。
and control and situational
它用于交换指挥和控制以及情境意识应用程序。
awareness applications.
意识应用程序。
So you can think of it as
因此你可以将其视为
an application running on a handheld.
一款运行在手持设备上的应用程序。
There's a map interface.
它有一个地图界面。
Users can exchange chat messages,
用户可以交换聊天消息，
images, other's position,
图片，别人的位置，
location information displayed on
位置信息显示在
the map and traditionally,
地图上通常显示的是，
there's a client server architecture
通常有一个客户端-服务器架构
within the TAK ecosystem that SHARE
在TAK生态系统中，SHARE
integrated with TAK we move towards
在TAK生态系统的整合下，我们向前迈进
the MINC data networking
MINC数据网络
paradigms and here you'll
范式和在这里你会
see that data is
看到那些数据是
requested based on interests and the data is
根据兴趣请求的，而且数据是
cached on the handheld devices and
缓存在手持设备上并且
at strategic points on the network and
储存在网络的战略节点上并且
those dashed lines really is
存储在网络的战略节点上并且那些虚线确实是代表在战术网络中的意思，
meant to represent in a tactical network,
意味着在战术网络中代表的，
you have links coming up and down.
你有上下链接。
You have a lot of mobility.
你的移动性很强。
Again, you have very intermittent links
您的链接非常间歇性。
that will having the ability to
那将具有能力去
cache data on the phone
在手机上缓存数据
is really invaluable in this setting.
在这种环境下确实非常宝贵。
Another offshoot of the SHARE work has been
SHARE工作的另一个分支已经是
a collaboration with another part of
与另一个部分的合作
the DOD and that's been and are
国防部，这已经是并且是
marrying up SHARE capabilities
整合共享能力
with 5G technologies.
与5G技术相结合。
As part of the SHARE programs,
作为SHARE项目的一部分，
we've demonstrated the secure isolation
我们已经展示了安全隔离
on the phone with those secure enclaves.
我们已经展示了安全隔离，通过电话与那些安全飞地进行了结合。
But then we've also married it up with
但我们也将其与
the network slicing concept.
网络切片概念。
In the figure that you see here, again,
在你这里看到的图中，再次，
you can see those end user devices
您可以看到那些终端用户设备
are viewing with
正在查看
the SHARE software and then further
共享软件然后进一步
isolating data as it traverses
隔离数据在其传输过程中
the network is this concept
网络是这个概念
of network slicing.
的网络切片。
We have had demonstrations
我们已经进行了演示
showcasing the value of
展示其价值
MINC data networking with
MINC数据网络连接~!@#$%^&*()
the secure slicing and
安全切片和
that's some work that we've
我们已经完成了一些工作，
actually wrapped up as
我们实际上已经完成了
up the SHARE program.
完成了SHARE项目。
Just to tie a bow on the SHARE work again,
再次为SHARE项目画上句号，
as we're wrapping up
我们正式结束
the SHARE phase of work and moving
我们正式结束共享阶段的工作，并继续进入我的新项目MINC。
on into my new program MINC.
我们正在过渡到我的新项目MINC。
DARPA is transitioning.
DARPA正在进行转型。
We've been working with
我们一直在合作
the 75th Ranger Regiment and
我们一直在合作，第75 Ranger团和美国陆军的其他部分
parts of the US Army
美国陆军的部分
on their specific use cases,
针对他们的具体使用案例，
and we will be transitioning
我们将会过渡
technology to various elements of the DoD.
将技术应用到国防部的各个元素中。
We are continuing
我们正在继绀
our conversations with NIST.
我们正在继续我们与NIST的对话。
As a community,
作为一个社区，
we're very eager to stay involved,
我们非常渴望继续参与进来，
and I think there will be opportunities as I
和我认为将会有机会当我
transition to my MINC program
过渡到我的MINC项目
to continue that involvement.
继续参与其中。
Let me tell you about MINC.
让我来告诉你关于MINC的事情。
MINC is a newer program.
MINC是一个较新的程序。
It was announced in
它是在今年的四月时间框架内宣布的。
the April timeframe of this year.
今年四月的时间框架内。
We have not yet announced
我们还没有宣布
who has been selected for the program,
我们还没有宣布谁被选中参加这个项目，but looking forward to announcing that soon.
but looking forward to announcing that soon.
但我们期待不久后就能宣布这一消息。
MINC stands for mission
MINC代表任务
integrated network control.
集成网络控制。
The two main objectives of MINC is
MINC的两个主要目标是
to make it easier to
使其更容易
initially configure a network,
最初配置一个网络，
but then to also be able to
但随后也能够
adopt that network benefit you.
采纳那个网络将会对你有益。
The networks that I'm talking about, again,
我再次提到的网络，
are these very heterogeneous
这些非常异构吗？
tactical networks
战术网络
that are composed of a lot of
由许多构成
legacy hardware,
遗留硬件，
a lot of legacy tactical radios,
许多遗留的战术无线电设备，
which make it a particularly
它们特别使其成为一个
challenging problem.
具有挑战性的问题。
Again, there's contrast between
再次，存在对比之间
today and what the program would provide.
今天以及程序将会提供的内容。
Today we have very much,
今天我们有很多内容，
high load war fighting,
高负荷战斗,
networking and security domains,
网络和安全领域，
and we want to get to a future where
我们希望迈向一个未来，在那里
we have seamless connectivity,
我们拥有无缝连接的能力，
where we can seamlessly bring up
我们可以无缝地引入
a link as we build effects chains,
我们构建效果链时可以无缝地加入一个环节，
being able to provide the cons in
在构建效果链时能够无缝地加入一个环节，为那些效果链提供网络支持。
networking for those effects chain.
为那些效果链提供网络支持。
There are really two key characteristics
有两个真正关键的特征
having to do with MINC.
与MINC有关。
The first is this idea of an always
这个想法首先是关于一个始终存在的~!@#$%^&*()
on secure control overlay.
这个想法首先是关于一个始终存在的~!@#$%^&*(), 在安全控制覆盖层上的目的。
The purpose of that control
这个控制的目的
overlay is to be able
覆盖层的目的是能够
to discover network resources,
用于发现网络资源，
whether that be CMS, compute or storage.
无论是内容管理系统（CMS）、计算还是存储。
Then the second characteristic
那么第二个特点
is to be able to compose
是能够编写
these network resources on
这些网络资源在
demand into a network of networks.
需求转化为一个网络中的网络。
Hopefully you're already starting
希望你已经开始了
to visualize this idea of
为了形象化这个想法
a software programmable software-defined
一种软件可编程的软件定义
networking type of environments.
网络类型的环境。
But we're actually trying to reimagine
但我们实际上正在尝试重新构想
software-defined networking for the DoD.
为美国国防部定义的软件网络。
Back to this idea that
回到这个想法上来说，
we have heterogeneous networks
我们拥有异构网络。
with legacy equipment in
与传统设备相结合
contrast to commercial networks,
与商业网络相比，
and the software-defined networking
与商业网络相比，软件定义网络
paradigm within commercial networks,
在商业网络中的范式，
you could have many different data plans,
你可以有多种不同的数据套餐，
many different control planes,
多种不同的控制平面，
so we need to be able to connect those
所以我们需要能够连接那些
together with a secure control overlay.
与一个安全的控制覆盖层相连接。
That's really what the first part
这确实是第一部分
of MINC is trying to do with
MINC正在尝试做的事情是
the first focus area MINC is trying to do.
MINC正在尝试做的事情的第一个重点领域是。
Of course, give
当然，给
an awareness of network resources,
对网络资源的认识，
so being able to discover
所以能够发现
those network resources and
那些网络资源和
have the means to task
有完成任务的方法
those network resources,
那些网络资源，
that would all come from
那些都将来源于
a management plane or
一个管理平面或
some orchestration framework.
一些编排框架。
Hopefully, again,
希望如此，再一次。
alluded to software-defined networking
提到了软件定义网络
before I got to it,
在我开始之前，
and now hopefully you're starting to
现在希望你开始慢慢地
envision an opportunity for things
设想一种事物的机会
like name data networking or
像名称、数据、网络这样的一般概念
general constructs like
such as names, data, networks
information-centric networking.
信息中心网络。
The idea with MINC is that we can
我们可以利用MINC的想法是
use information-centric networking or
利用信息中心网络或者
name data networking specifically
利用信息中心网络或者专门的数据网络来实现
to be able to compose
利用信息中心网络或者专门的数据网络来实现，能够构建安全控制覆盖层，该层覆盖在...上。
that security control overlay that rides
on top of the underlying security control overlay that rides
on top of the underlying
在底层之上
heterogeneous networks.
异构网络。
Some other concepts that we're
我们正在探索的一些其他概念包括
bringing in from the commercial space
从商业领域引入
include network function virtualization,
包括网络功能虚拟化，
which goes hand in hand with STN,
它与STN（软件定义网络）密切相关，
and also this idea of
以及这个想法
an intent-driven networking.
意图驱动的网络。
Within MINC, we really want to
在MINC内部，我们真的想要
reimagine intent-driven networking
重新构想以意图为驱动的网络连接
as mission-driven networking.
作为以使命为驱动的网络连接。
How can we go from
我们如何从作为以使命为驱动的网络连接转变为将使命目标转化为网络目标？
mission objectives to network objectives?
将使命目标转化为网络目标？
That then we read it over as part of
那么我们作为一部分仔细阅读它
the management plane or as part of what we're
管理平面或作为我们正在进行的一部分
calling distributed network
调用分布式网络
orchestration in MINC.
在MINC中进行编排。
In addition to the secure control overlay,
除了安全控制覆盖层之外，
I talked a bit about that.
我稍微谈了一下那个。
That's our focus areas 1.
我们的重点领域是1。
Now that we have this ability
现在我们拥有了这种能力
to reprogram in software,
重新在软件中编程，
we have this ability to
我们有这种能力去
discover resiliently and reliably
发现网络资源，并且能够坚韧可靠地发现
discover network resources and
发现网络资源并且
actually cached data about
实际上缓存了有关数据
those network resources and
这些网络资源和
their associated control parameters.
他们相关的控制参数。
We now have this opportunity to
我们现在有这个机会去
employ distributed network orchestration.
成为那个分布式网络的一部分来进行管理。
Part of that distributed network
成为那个分布式网络的一部分
orchestration is not only
编排不仅仅是
configuring the underlying radios
配置底层无线电设备
that are forming these networks,
正在形成这些网络的设备，
but then to also
但也要
potentially recommend movement of
建议调动
communications assets to better
更好地利用通信资源
enable networking and communications.
启用网络和通信。
Then another component of focus area
那么另一个关注点是
2 is not only managing the network,
那么另一个关注点是不仅要管理网络，but the data or information as well.
but the data or information as well.
但也要管理数据或信息。
In the spirit of network
在网络精神中
function virtualization,
功能虚拟化，
we're generalizing that contract to include
我们正在将该合同泛化以包括
network information and security management.
网络信息与安全管理。
Then of course, I talked a bit about
Then of course, I talked a bit about ~!@#$%^&*()
intent-driven networking
面向意图的网络
on military missions,
在军事任务中，
and that's folded into focus area 3,
这被纳入到重点领域3中，
which will be integrating
这将会被整合进
all of this into a system.
这一切将会被整合进一个系统。
Just a quick time check.
只是快速确认一下时间。
I just have two slides left.
我只剩下两张幻灯片了。
As I mentioned, we
我提到过，我们
haven't announced who is
还没有宣布谁是
selected for the program yet,
尚未选定参加该计划的人选，
but we will be kicking off
但我们将在接下来的几个月启动该计划。
the program in the next few months.
我们将在接下来的几个月启动该计划。
I'm very much looking forward
我非常期待在接下来的几个月启动该计划，直到一年后能够
to a year from now being able to
看到一年后能够
report about the progress
报告关于进展情况
that we've made in using and
我们在使用和应用方面取得的进展情况
applying name data networking concepts
应用命名数据网络概念
to forming a secure control overlay.
形成一个安全的控制覆盖层。
That's what we'll be building
这就是我们将要构建的内容。
out in Phase 1,
我们将在第一阶段推出。
really focusing on
真正专注于
that secure control overlay and developing
那个安全控制覆盖层以及正在开发的
a MINC-enabled Blue Force network
一个支持MINC的蓝军网络
situational awareness application.
态势感知应用程序。
As the program progresses,
随着程序的推进，
we'll be continuing to
我们将继续进行
develop out the algorithms and maturing
我们将继续进行开发算法和完善它们的能力，并增加。
the capabilities and adding
我们将继续增强功能并且添加
more and more MINC-enabled applications
越来越多支持MINC的应用程序
as the phases progress.
随着各个阶段的推进。
Last but not least,
最后但同样重要的是，
I talked about my SHARE slide,
我谈到了我的SHARE幻灯片，
how we've worked with
我们是如何合作的
the 75th Ranger Regiment,
第75游骑兵团，
and we want to continue that momentum in
我们希望继续保持这种势头在
the MINC program and really make MINC
我们希望继续保持这种势头在MINC项目中，并真正发展MINC，根据操作员所了解的情况进行调整。
informed by what the operator
了解到的情况来指导
is looking for and to be able
正在寻找并且有能力~!@#$%^&*()
to fill that need at the tactical edge.
满足战术边缘的需求。
Back over to you, Chandler.
回到你这边了，钱德勒。
>> Thank you, Dr. Schurgot.
>> 谢谢你，舒尔戈特博士。
I don't see any questions
我没有看到任何问题。
in the chat, but I have one real quick.
在聊天中我没有看到任何问题，但我这里有一个很快速的问题。
In terms of lessons learned from
在吸取的教训方面
the SHARE program and how
the SHARE program 和如何~!@#$%^&*()
that could be fed back into their community,
可以反馈到他们的社区中，
could you speak a little bit on
可以稍微谈一谈在那里做了些什么吗？
what was done there.
在那里做了些什么。
>> Sure. We've talked
>> 当然。我们已经在其他社区会议上讨论过这个问题，
about this at other community meetings,
已经在其他社区会议上讨论过这个问题，
but the SHARE performers,
但是SHARE表演者，
the actual folks developing
实际上是那些正在开发的人员
the capabilities have made
实际上是那些正在开发的人员，the capabilities have made some enhancements and changes.
some enhancements and changes
一些增强和变更
to the underlying NDN codebase.
对底层NDN代码库进行了增强和变更。
We have added things
我们已经增加了一些功能。
like persistent subscriptions,
像持久订阅，
which I know is a little against
它我知道有点违背了
the NDN paradigm,
NDN范式，
a bit controversial amongst this crowd.
在这个群体中有点有争议。
But we have made
但我们已经取得了
additional security improvements and
我们已经取得了额外的安全改进和
the long-term goal is to be able to get
实现长期目标是能够获得
the best of breed solution from
业界领先的解决方案来自
SHARE and potentially MINC and really
分享和可能的MINC，以及确实
contribute that back to
为之做出贡献回馈给
the community and work towards
为社区做出贡献并努力工作以实现
a more standardized DoD
更标准化的DoD(国防部)
and NDN type capability.
和NDN类型的能力。
>> That's awesome. Thank you, Dr. Schurgot.
>> 太棒了。谢谢你，舒尔戈特博士。
to our next speaker.
我们下一位演讲嘉宾。
Our next talk is by Mohammed Elbadry.
我们下一位演讲嘉宾是穆罕默德·埃尔巴德里。
It's Towards a Unification
它是朝着统一的方向发展
of Name and Address Based Communication.
的名称和地址基于通信。
Let me just read the bio of Mohammed.
让我来读一下穆罕默德的简介。
He is a PhD candidate at
他是一名博士研究生，在
Computer Engineering department
计算机工程系
of Stony Brook University.
斯托尼布鲁克大学。
His research focuses on
他的研究重点是
wireless medium Access Control
无线介质访问控制
design. On to you sir.
设计。转交给您了，先生。
>> Thank you very much.
>> 非常感谢您。
Let me share my screen.
让我分享我的屏幕。
Can you see the slides?
你能看到幻灯片吗？
>> I can see it from my end.
>> 我这边可以看到。
>> Hi, everyone. I'll be going over,
>> 大家好。我将要过去，
Toward Unification of Name
走向名称的统一
and Address Based Communication.
和基于地址的通信。
The motivation behind the work is that
工作背后的动机是
an NFD has been out for multiple years.
NFD已经推出多年了。
There is a mature codebase
有一个成熟的代码库
right now that's available that
现在可用的是
anyone can use with
现在可用的是任何人都可以使用的
a lot of features and a
很多功能和一个
lot capabilities and that's with layer.
很多功能和那是与层相结合的。
However, the industry hasn't fully
然而，这个行业还没有完全
adopted NFD due to decades of
采纳了NFD，这是由于几十年来的
vested interest in TCP/IP network
既得利益者对TCP/IP网络的兴趣
and they've already done
他们已经完成了
development and transition
发展与过渡
costs would be a lot.
成本会很高。
What we believe NFD needs is
我们认为NFD需要的是
a success story where address-based
我们认为NFD需要的是一个成功故事，其中基于地址的 [inaudible] pretty much knocked it out of the park;
[inaudible] pretty much not out of the park;
~!@#$%^&*()
there is no competition or a chance
没有竞争或机会。
for address-based stack to compete at all.
要想基于地址的栈有任何竞争力。
For us to do that,
为了做到这一点，
we looked at where name-based can excel.
我们考察了基于名称的方法在哪些领域可以表现出色。
One of the fields that
我们考察了基于名称的方法在哪些领域可以表现出色。其中一个领域是
in industry is starting to form but
在工业领域开始形成，但是
hasn't fully developed yet is
尚未完全发展
basically decentralized wild edges.
基本上是去中心化的野生边缘。
A lot of other presenters
很多其他的演讲者
before me also covered.
在我之前也有很多其他的演讲者涉及过这个话题。
The reasons are standard procedures
这些原因是标准程序。
are still in the formation process.
仍然处于形成过程中。
There is not a well-known
还没有一个众所周知的
tested procedure on how to do things or
尚未经过测试的操作程序或方法
not well known address-based libraries that
不太知名的基于地址的库，可以让人们直接去
people can just go to
直接去
and that solves their problem,
并且这解决了他们的问题，
articles, or salesforce.
文章，或者是Salesforce。
An edge name-based
基于边缘命名的
multicast dissemination also
多播传播也是
needed one to many communication
需要一对多通信
is a problem on the edge.
边缘上存在一个问题。
That address-based communication hasn't
边缘上存在一个问题。基于地址的通信还没有真正提供一个解决方案。
really provided a solution for
真正提供了一个解决方案给
just due to the nature also
仅仅由于其本质特性
limitations of address-based communication.
地址式通信的局限性。
Essentially, we have
本质上，我们有
address-based communication where
基于地址的通信在哪里
the industry is and we have
行业是这样的，我们拥有
the name-based communication,
基于名称的沟通，
which is essentially
这本质上是
our goal to transition to
我们的目标是过渡到~!@#$%^&*()
and what we need is essentially a bridge.
我们需要的本质上是一座桥梁。
How do we get industry there.
我们如何才能将产业带到那里。
I heard earlier that there
我早些时候听说那里~!@#$%^&*()
was a conversation, debate,
之前有一场对话、辩论，
discussion between multiple libraries
多个图书馆之间的讨论
or one big library in
或者支持一个大型图书馆在
favor of a small TCP/IP library
支持一个小型的TCP/IP库
was tweaking name-based services.
正在调整基于名称的服务。
The idea of it is to introduce
这个想法是为了介绍
industry people who are using pretty much
业界人士普遍使用的
TCP/IP stack and address-based communication
TCP/IP协议栈和基于地址的通信
to name-based communication in the benefits
的优势
of name-based communication without
基于名称的通信而无需
transitioning everything so that way it
转换一切，以便它
gets small services that name-based
变得更加出色
excels over
优于
address-based communication easily.
基于地址的通信很容易。
A simple API would be
一个简单的API将会是
data multicast dissemination on the edge.
数据在边缘的多点传播。
Right now, data dissemination on
the edge is a critical aspect, especially when it involves wireless communication.
the edge specifically when it's wireless,
边缘尤其是在它是无线的时候，
edge communication, edge to edge,
边缘通信，边缘对边缘，
there is no good system side broadcast
没有好的系统侧广播
which is not reliable.
它不可靠。
But if there's an API similar to the sample,
但如果有一个类似于样本的API，
which just takes the file
它只需要取得文件
and handles of course,
并当然处理好把手，
all the assembly and fragmentation,
所有的组装和分解工作，
developers would be up to try
开发者们愿意尝试
it at least to see how it goes and
开发者们愿意尝试，至少看一下它的运行情况和
how it works and without
它的工作原理以及不需要更改所有其他
changing all those other
更改所有那些其他
communication and transitioning.
沟通和过渡。
The other thing I want to cover is,
我想要讲的另一件事是，
instead of looking at name-based stack,
而不是看基于名称的堆栈，
I want to consider looking
我想考虑看看
at a unified paradigm.
在一个统一的范式中。
What I mean by unifying paradigm
我所说的统一范式
is address-based and name-based in one.
是基于地址和基于名称相结合的。
The reason why we started looking
我们开始探索的原因
at unified paradigm instead of
采用统一范式而不是
name-based is that because Access Control
基于名称的访问控制是因为
on the edge is
在边缘是
pretty much transmitter initiates.
发射器基本上是启动者。
So you need to communicate to someone;
所以你需要和某人交流；
you send an ID and
你发送一个身份证明和
you send data to the Access Control.
你向访问控制发送数据。
There's other use case which we're
有其他使用案例我们非常熟悉，
very familiar with,
我们非常熟悉的，
which is applications
我们非常熟悉的，是应用程序正在多播数据驱动。
are multicasting data driven.
正在多播数据驱动。
So receiver initiates and
接收方发起并且
that's where name-based,
那就是基于名称的地方，
you subscribe to data and you get data.
你订阅数据，然后你就会收到数据。
Now these two, one is transmitter
现在这两个中，一个是发射器
initiated and other one
发起的，另一个是
is receiver initiated,
是接收方发起的，
one is address-based and one
一个是基于地址的，另一个
is pretty much data-driven.
是几乎完全基于数据驱动的。
We started looking at MAC layer,
我们开始研究MAC层，
this is purely MAC layer
这是纯粹的MAC层
medium Access Control and we start
介质访问控制，我们开始
looking at Unified paradigm MAC layer
统一范式介质访问控制层
and looked at algorithms that exist
并研究了现有的算法
that MAC layer needs
该MAC层需要
to pretty much operate and do.
需要基本上运行和执行。
Rate control algorithms and reliability,
速率控制算法和可靠性，
beamforming, frame aggregation,
波束成形，帧聚合，
and a lot more.
还有很多其他的内容。
But we started focusing
但我们开始专注
on these and we started building
在这些基础上，我们开始构建
a small layer called algorithm adaptation
一个名为算法适应的小层
layer and we connected
层，并且我们连接了
all of these algorithms too.
我们也连接了所有这些算法。
We started saying, can we
我们开始提问，我们能否
apply the same algorithm
应用相同的算法
with the smaller adaptive layer so
使用较小的自适应层，因此
we can deploy the same algorithm
我们可以部署相同的算法
on name-based and address-based?
在基于名称和基于地址的情况下？
We're actually able to
我们实际上能够
demonstrate a little bit right now.
我们实际上能够现在就演示一点。
We took one of the examples which is
我们拿出了一个例子，这个例子是
rate control algorithm and we'll
速率控制算法，我们将会讨论我们如何能够部署
discuss how we can deploy
讨论我们如何能够部署
that algorithm same exact algorithm's
该算法与同一算法的
minor adaptation from address-based
该算法与同一算法的细微调整从基于地址的通信转变为基于名称的通信。
to name-based communication,
将基于地址的通信转变为基于名称的通信，
why it's important.
为什么这很重要。
We cover what is rate control.
我们讲解什么是速率控制。
Imagine you have two radios,
想象你有两台收音机，
Node A and Node B and
Node A与Node B以及
Node A is trying to send data to
Node A正在尝试向
Node B in Wi-Fi or 8211.
Node B在Wi-Fi或8211中。
What data rate to transmit at?
应该以什么数据速率进行传输？
There are a lot of
有很多
data rates that you can transmit
您可以传输的数据速率
that and the selection
该选择
is usually based on a table.
通常是基于一张表格。
You change the modulation,
你改变了调制方式，
you change the code rate,
你改变了码率，
the spatial streams, error coding,
空间流，错误编码，
and then you get different data rates.
然后你会得到不同的数据传输速率。
Usually that change is
通常那种改变是
done verifying conditions.
完成了条件验证。
So you have a packet, you send
所以你有一个数据包，你发送了
fragment and its multiple frames,
片段及其多个帧，
and then you change it based
然后你根据情况进行相应的改变，
on the medium condition,
在中等条件下，
so you change dynamically.
所以你会动态变化。
Sometimes the condition is very good,
有时候状态非常好，
you transmit at 600 Mbps and then it drops
你的传输速率是600 Mbps，然后它下降了。
down to 15 as
降到了15 Mbps。
the connection is not so good anymore.
连接不再那么好了。
The way it works is that basically
它的工作原理基本上是这样的
Node B before the A starts to transmit to B,
A开始传输到B之前的节点B，
it will basically share supported rates,
它基本上会共享支持的速率，
B will say I can receive some data rates.
B会说我可以接收一些数据速率。
Let's say in this table we have 1, 6,
假设在这个表格中我们有1, 6,
9, 24, 54 Mbps.
9, 24, 54 Mbps.
Now, it will start transmitting.
现在，它将开始传输。
What it will do is
它将要做的是
that it will search for as many
它将要搜索尽可能多的
first frame at some data rate.
首帧以某种数据速率。
If it gets acknowledgement,
如果它得到了确认，
that means it received it by
这意味着它通过接收到了
higher data rate for the lower data rate.
更高的数据速率用于较低的数据速率。
As a scenario walks through,
当场景逐步展开时，
it's sends at nine Mbps.
它以每秒9兆比特的速度发送。
It passes, it goes to
它通过，它前往~!@#$%^&*()
a higher one which is pretty much 24 Mbps.
一个更高的，大约是24 Mbps。
If it loses it,
如果它丢失了数据，
it'll try to retransmit
它会尝试重新传输
the same frame at a lower data rates.
它会以较低的数据速率重新传输相同的帧。
If it passes,
如果它通过了，
it continues and then it goes up.
它继续前进，然后向上走。
This is a simple algorithm
这是一个简单的算法。
which is essentially go up or
这本质上是上升还是~!@#$%^&*()
down and that's quite using
下来，这确实是相当使用的。
unicast and address-based communication.
单播和基于地址的通信。
Now, what about name-based rate control?
现在，基于名称的速率控制又是怎样的呢？
We don't have any ID, so we
我们没有任何身份证明，所以我们~!@#$%^&*()
don't know who's A who is B,
我们不知道谁是A谁是B。
we don't know who we're sending to.
我们不知道我们在发送给谁。
We don't know who the receivers are.
我们不知道接收者是谁。
We don't know if it's one receiver
我们不知道是不是只有一个接收者。
or multiple receivers.
或者有多个接收者。
We could technically restore rate controls.
我们技术上可以恢复费率控制。
Every time we get new interests,
每次我们获得新的兴趣，
we could restart the rate control and
我们可以重新启动速率控制并且
assume it's new number
假设它是新号码
of receivers or set of receivers,
接收者或一组接收者，
and start trying to
开始尝试去
find the optimal data rate.
寻找最优的数据传输速率。
The problem is that the data
问题是数据 ~!@#$%^&*()
packet is very small.
数据包非常小。
That by the time final optimal data rate,
到最终的最佳数据传输速率时，
we'll have to restart again
我们将不得不再次重新启动。
because the data packet ended.
因为数据包已经结束了。
What we ended up doing is
我们最终做的是
embed an ID information
嵌入一个ID信息
per interest to allow read
根据兴趣允许阅读
control and we don't use that for filtering.
我们不使用它来进行过滤控制。
It's still name-based communication.
它仍然是基于名称的通信。
We use ID just
我们仅仅使用ID
internally to
内部地
actually recognize who we're sending to.
实际上要识别我们要派遣的人。
It's basically to identify
实际上要识别
general centric information.
一般中心信息。
What that enabled us to do is that
这使我们能够
now we can identify each node
现在我们可以识别每个节点
internally and we were actually able
在内部，我们实际上能够
to use the address-based
使用基于地址的
read control algorithms
读取控制算法
that have already been
已经
designed and tested as a black box.
设计并以黑盒方式进行测试。
Use the ID that we obtained for
使用我们获得的ID来进行
the packets, supported rates,
使用我们获得的ID来进行数据包，支持的速率，
and history and obtain a data rate to control
和历史记录并获得一个数据速率来进行控制
the data rate for a name-based communication.
基于名称的通信的数据速率。
That way we can send name-based frames
这样我们就可以发送基于名称的帧
with rate control that's been
具有已经开发出的速率控制功能，
developed for address-based communication.
开发用于基于地址的通信。
What we obtained from these results
我们从这些结果中获得了什么
is that if we just use broadcast
如果我们仅仅使用广播
where we use
我们使用在哪里
name-based communication without actually
基于名称的通信而无需实际
identifying the note we are sending
识别我们正在发送的便条
to and using great control,
并使用极大的控制力，
the latency of 30 seconds
延迟30秒
by the unified stack transmission,
通过统一堆栈传输，
we got it down to 0.9 seconds.
我们将其减少到了0.9秒。
The loss rate is 12-20 percent,
损失率为12-20%。
which is just broadcast because we're able
这只是广播，因为我们能够利用单播传输。
to leverage the unicast transmission.
利用单播传输。
We have one consumer,
我们有一个消费者，
one producer transmission,
一个生产者传输，
we're able to get the loss rate down,
我们能够降低损失率，
and we were also able to get
同时我们也能够让
the medium utilization down at the same time.
我们也能够降低介质的利用率。
One of the main reasons
我们也能够降低介质的利用率，主要原因之一是在你进行广播传输时，~!@#$%^&*()
is when you're transmitting at broadcasts,
是当你在进行广播传输时，
you pretty much transmit at base rate
你基本上是以基础速率进行传输
one Mbps, six Mbps.
一兆比特每秒，六兆比特每秒。
But when you do the rate control,
但当你进行速率控制时，
which means at a much higher rate,
这意味着以一个更高的速率，
65 Mbps and can go up to 600 Mbps.
65 Mbps，最高可达600 Mbps。
Essentially, rate control algorithm is
本质上，速率控制算法是
critical for
至关重要的
good performance wireless communication,
良好性能的无线通信，
and we need long pretty much communication
我们需要长时间的、几乎无缝的通信
across multiple data frames.
跨越多个数据帧。
It finds the optimal rate and doesn't
它找到了最优的速率，但并没有
restart again or the overhead is too much.
重新开始或者开销太大。
We started looking at
我们开始查看
existing access that exist
现有的访问权限
in the MAC layer to form a unified stack.
在MAC层形成统一的协议栈。
What we have is filtering.
我们拥有的是过滤功能。
We can do name and address-based filtering.
我们可以进行基于姓名和地址的过滤。
We could do discovery,
我们可以进行发现，
which can be attribute-based
它可以是基于属性的。
discovery for address-based communication.
发现基于地址的通讯。
We could do read control for unicast,
我们可以对单播进行读取控制，
multicast robustness protocol designs.
我们还可以进行多播的健壮性协议设计。
We also could do
robustness protocol design for multicasting.
single consumer producer selection.
单一消费者生产者选择。
Frame aggregation.
帧聚合。
This is an address-based communication,
这是一个基于地址的通信方式，
and that's basically you package
这基本上就是你打包
your multiple frames together to
将你的多个帧组合在一起以
form an MPDU,
将多个帧组合成一个MPDU，
and that's where
而那就是在哪里
higher data rate transmission is
高速率数据传输是
absolutely necessary. Beam forming.
绝对必要的。波束成形。
That's when you have multiple antennas and
这就是当你有多个天线并且
you want to send in a specific direction.
你想要向一个特定方向发送。
What needs to be done and still is
需要做的事情还有
missing is multicast rate control,
缺少的是多播速率控制，
the multi-consumer producer selection.
缺少的是多播速率控制，我们提供了多消费者生产者选择。
In short, we provided
简而言之，我们提供了
a way to possibility to attract
一种可能吸引行业专业人士的方式
industry professional by targeting
行业专业人士的目标
edge market and a specific APIs to just
边缘市场和特定的API来仅仅
provide name-based services instead
提供基于名称的服务来代替
of the whole stack to attract people,
吸引人们使用整个技术栈，
and then eventually moved to the whole stack.
并最终转向整个技术栈。
Proposal for
提案书
a lightweight name-based services and
一个基于轻量级名称的服务及
marketing for low barrier entry
面向低门槛进入的市场营销
and immediate benefit,
和即时利益，
and a unified MAC that benefits
和一个统一的MAC，它有益于
both name and address-based communication.
名称和地址的通信方式。
Thank you.
谢谢。
>> Thank you. I have a question, real quick.
谢谢。我有个问题，很快。
It is, did you evaluate this
它是的，你评估了这个吗？
more or less qualitatively or you
或多或少定性地，或者你
actually end up trying to
实际上最终尝试去
prototype any piece of it.
实际上最终尝试去原型化它的任何部分。>> We did actually prototype any piece of it.
>> We did actually prototypes.
我们确实制作了原型。
The slide that had the latency lost trait
幻灯片丢失了延迟特性。
and medium utilization and
和中等利用率
policies were actually
实施的政策实际上是
obtained from real system.
从真实系统中获得。
We build a system on
我们在一个树莓派上构建了一个系统，它是一个初级丛林，
and you modify the firmware and the kernel,
并且你修改了固件和内核，
remove the existing address space stack
移除现有的地址空间栈
and then actually performed the experiments.
然后实际进行了实验。
>> That's very cool. All right,
那非常酷。好的，
sounds good. Thank you so much.
听起来不错。非常感谢你。
>> Thank you.
>> 谢谢你。
>> Our final speaker.
>> 我们的最后一位演讲者。
This is POC followed by, I believe a demo.
这是一个概念验证（POC），接下来我相信会有一个演示。
The POC is NEAR platform supporting
这个概念验证是NEAR平台的支持
augmented reality over NDN by Jinghao Zhao.
增强现实在NDN上的应用，作者：Jinghao Zhao。
He is a fourth year PhD student at UCLA.
他是加州大学洛杉矶分校的一名四年级博士研究生。
Research interests include
研究兴趣包括
mobile edge systems,
移动边缘系统，
wireless networks, and mobile security.
无线网络和移动安全。
Onto you, I think you
向你看齐，我想你
have a demo; is that right?
进行一次演示；是这样吗？
>> Yes.
>> 是的。
>> All right.
>> 好的。
>> Let me share my screen
>> 让我分享我的屏幕
[OVERLAPPING] right now.
[重叠的对话] 正在进行中。
>> I think you are [inaudible].
>> 我认为你是[听不清]。
>> Yeah. Everyone,
是的。各位，
I'm glad to introduce
很高兴介绍
our latest work and I am Jinghao from UCLA.
我们的最新研究，我是来自加州大学洛杉矶分校的景浩。
Today I'm going to introduce
今天我将要介绍
the NEAR platforms NDN wireless,
NEAR平台的NDN无线，
AR Platforms to you.
面向您的AR平台。
Keeping the requirements of
保持对~!@#$%^&*()的要求
the high-quality AR contents and
高品质的AR内容和
the mobile edge computing
移动边缘计算
actually provides us in
实际上为我们提供了
new opportunities for it's
为其提供了新的机会
leverage easy accelerator's,
利用简易加速器的，
storage, and also
存储，以及还有
the more management functions.
更多的管理功能。
For the January Edge AR systems,
一月份的Edge AR系统，
which you already requires first in to
您已经首先需要进入~!@#$%^&*()
support virus AR applications.
支持病毒AR应用程序。
For example, is a merging
例如，是一种合并
likes a remote training
喜欢远程培训
the industrial wearables and also sound
工业穿戴设备以及声音
AR gains assisted by the Edge Server.
边缘服务器辅助的AR增强。
Also the Edge server need to handle
边缘服务器还需要处理
this high dynamic from this mobile devices
这些移动设备产生的高动态性
like the user mobility or
像用户的移动性或
some workload mobility or
一些工作负载的移动性或
even network dynamics
甚至是网络动态变化
and application processing.
和应用处理。
Also for that one,
还有那个，
which the AR requires,
需要AR的，
the Edge Server has
边缘服务器具有
a very low network latency and also
具有非常低的网络延迟，同时也
the high bandwidth to support
具有高带宽以支持
its high-quality AR contents.
具有高带宽以支持当前AR系统所需的高质量AR内容。
To harbor for the current AR systems,
为了适应当前的AR系统，
it's more like for example,
它更像是举个例子，
it involves crossly or information slides.
它涉及到交叉或信息幻灯片。
The application's needs the cost of
应用程序需要成本用于
processing and also for the network systems,
处理以及用于网络系统的费用，
it also involves crossly or likes to
它也涉及交叉或喜欢~!@#$%^&*()
transport layer and also the lower layer,
传输层以及更低层次，
the physical layer, even the max needs
物理层，甚至最大需求
some higher the information
~!@#$%^&*()
for better optimization.
为了更好的优化。
However, the current system
然而，当前系统
has this multi-layered indirection cannot,
这种多层次的间接性无法，
more like share information course
更像是分享信息的课程
these contents to the network and vice versa.
这些内容传输到网络上，反之亦然。
The second is that the current limitation is
当前的限制是
the virus applications and
病毒应用程序和
also the developers using the same ash,
还有开发者使用相同的ash，
you really need to develop
你真的需要开发
your own security schemes
你自己的安全方案
and also the network stacks,
以及网络堆栈，
different processing
不同的处理方式
management, even a security.
管理，甚至是一种安全保障。
The way she is hard to manage
她的管理方式很难掌控。
for this IS system.
此外，我们还有许多配置可用于这个信息系统。
for the crossly or any prone to error.
此外，我们还有许多配置可用于这个信息系统。对于容易出错的部分，最后一个问题是——
The last issue is that
最后一个问题是——
for the current AR actually
目前实际上是这样的AR。
still using this unit
仍在使用这个单元。
cost-based delivery as the lower layer.
成本基础交付作为底层。
That's even a separate cost
这甚至是一项单独的成本
of wireless medium is still
无线介质仍然是
perform this unicast and
执行这种单播和
cannot scale to multiple users.
无法扩展到多个用户。
Especially for this narrows,
尤其是对于这种狭窄的情况，
who requires massive connections?
谁需要大量的连接？
For example, the theme park or
例如，主题公园或者
the commencements narrow in the campus.
毕业典礼在校园里举行得很隆重。
We want to peel the AR platform
我们想要剥离AR平台。
that supports the following features.
支持以下功能。
The first is that we want
我们首先想要
to elaborate data-centric transmission
阐述以数据为中心的传输
with the built-in multicasts support
具有内置的多播支持功能
to ensure scalability.
为了确保可扩展性。
Also we want to integrate the optimizations
我们还希望集成优化。
for different components and
为了不同的组件和
to build the system.
为了构建系统。
We want to integrate is in your wireless and
我们想要将其集成到你的无线中并且~!@#$%^&*()
the widh this crossly applications,
这些应用程序的宽度非常交叉。
accelerations and securities, et cetera.
加速和安全性等。
Also we want to provide
我们还想提供
this platform as an open source platform for
我们还想提供这个平台作为一个开放源代码平台，用于未来的发展以及为了
future developments and also for
未来的发展以及也为了
the performance comparison
性能比较
for future new designs.
为将来的新设计。
Here we introduce our integration efforts
这里我们介绍我们的集成工作努力。
as the NEAR platform,
作为NEAR平台，
the NDN wireless ultimately reality.
NDN无线最终现实。
Our platform includes
我们的平台包括
the following components.
以下几个组成部分。
The first is that we support
我们首先支持
different AR modules for
不同的AR模块用于
a virus AR applications.
不同的AR模块用于病毒AR应用程序。Also the network side that we apply,
Also the network side that we apply,
我们应用的网络方面，
the NDN wireless and with
我们应用的网络方面，NDN无线和高性能链路层组播。
the high-performance link-layer multicast
高性能链路层组播
as the basically transmission scheme.
作为基本的传输方案。
We also integrated GPU/
我们还集成了GPU/
FPGA based accelerators
基于FPGA的加速器
into our system and plus all the AR content.
集成到我们的系统中，并加入所有的AR内容。
Also the communications are
也是通信内容
using the name-based security.
使用基于名称的安全性。
Here is the overview of
这是概述
our basic system structure.
我们的基本系统结构。
The near platform containing
包含近平台的
the following components.
包含以下组件。
The first is that for the producer side,
生产者方面首先是，
we have the producers to publish
我们有制作人来发布
all the real-time camera views
所有实时摄像头视图
from its mobile cameras.
从其移动摄像头。
All the information was
所有信息都是
the camera frames will
相机帧将
be retrieved by
将被检索
the Edge Server and Edge Server performance,
边缘服务器和边缘服务器性能，
the AR module processing
增强现实模块处理
and with different tasks.
以及处理不同的任务。
Also leveraging
以及利用
these accelerations with GPU/FPGA.
这些加速是通过GPU/FPGA实现的。
After the processing of the AR contents
在AR内容处理之后
will be published through all the consumers.
将会被发布给所有的消费者。
As a consumer as are sharing
作为消费者，我们正在分享
the same contents will leveraging
相同的内容将会利用
this link-layer multicast either access
此链路层多播要么访问
points to retrieve this information
获取这些信息的要点
and all the contents are also protected by
以及所有内容也受到保护
the integrated security with NDN.
集成了NDN的安全性。
First these ads for,
首先是这些广告，
I we introduced likes
我们介绍了喜欢
the different overall modules,
我们介绍了不同的整体模块，and later I will introduce more details
and later I will introduce more details
稍后我会介绍更多细节
as far as our NEAR designs.
至于我们的NEAR设计。
First, as far as the AR Modules,
首先，就AR模块而言，
we will later show a demo video to show
稍后我们将展示一个演示视频来展示
the virus functions and also how is
how it is used in different industries.
the AR platform leveraging
该AR平台利用
that NDN for the processing and organization.
该NDN用于处理和组织。
Generally, we support the following modules,
通常，我们支持以下模块，
including the object phase
包括物体阶段
and post detection.
以及物体检测之后的阶段。
Also we support is
以及我们支持的是
3D model rendering and AR video overlay to
3D模型渲染和AR视频叠加到
more like party is this narrows
这更像是聚会，这样就缩小了
for the commercial product,
对于商业产品，
these planing and also for advertisements.
这些规划也用于广告宣传。
and multiple consumers scheme,
和多个消费者方案，
like using this sheer view.
喜欢使用这种透明视图。
For example, here in
例如，在这里
this sheer view functions,
这种纯粹的视角功能，
the two producers are
两位制片人是
producing this camera view
制作这个摄像机视角
from its own side,
从它自己的一侧，
but it's more like in a similar location.
但它更像是在一个相似的位置。
There are some sheered views inside it.
它里面有一些剪切视图。
As Edge server will retrieve
边缘服务器将会检索
the frames from the post streams and
将帧从发布流中检索出来并且
combine them together and
将它们组合在一起并且
moldy caused the streams to
发霉导致溪流变得
all the consumers to more
所有消费者更多地
like provide this panorama views.
喜欢提供这种全景视角。
We also support the chroma key video
我们也支持色键视频。
for the interaxial opera so that
为了交互式歌剧，以便
the consumers can more like watch
消费者可以更像是在观看
this opera ways these
~!@#$%^&*()
stages as their backgrounds,
舞台作为他们的背景，
which we will show demos later.
我们稍后将展示演示。
For all these AR contents
为了所有这些增强现实内容
to ensure the high-quality performers
为了确保高质量的表演者
and the way that a traditional
和传统方式
2D contents depend why is
~!@#$%^&*()
for each contents can as high as 40 Mbps.
每个内容的传输速率可高达40 Mbps。
For the recent likes the volumetric videos,
最近像体积视频这样的内容，
these directly streaming in the 3D models
这些直接在3D模型中进行流式传输。
from the edge to the consumer side.
从边缘到消费者端。
All the each client's needs,
满足每个客户的需求，
even nee [MUSIC] ds 100
满足每个客户的需求，即使需要100 Mbps to ensure as 30 FPS playout.
Mbps to ensure as 30 FPS playout.
Mbps以确保每秒30帧的播放。
Power for the current access points which
当前接入点的电力需求是为了支持具有双流MIMO技术的智能手机。
support the smartphones with a two-by-two MIMO.
它只能支持具有二乘二MIMO技术的智能手机。
It can only support very
它只能支持非常
limited like the numbers of clients.
它只能支持非常有限的客户数量。
For example,
例如，
for the highest physical layer rate
对于最高物理层速率
for the 802.11n,
对于802.11n，
it can only support
它只能支持
up to three users to enjoy this Phy rate AR.
它只能支持最多三个用户享受这种Phy速率AR。Even for the latest ax
Even for the latest ax
即使是最新的ax标准，
it can only support 12 users.
它只能支持12个用户。
Due to the protocol overhead,
由于协议开销，
here we just calculate
这里我们只是计算
the maximum numbers can be
可以是最大的数字
scored it's using this physical rates.
得分是使用这些物理速率。
Part of the protocol overheard plus the noise
协议中被监听到的部分加上噪音
and also cannot achieve
也无法实现
the highest rates when keep running
持续运行时的最高费率
this AR functions due to mobility and
这个增强现实功能得益于移动性和
we need the numbers will be further reduced.
我们需要的数字将会进一步减少。
Why important questions is that how we
我们为什么要问重要的问题是怎样我们
can scale our AR supports,
可以扩展我们的AR支持，
choose the modules and
选择模块和
even massive connections,
即使是庞大的连接，
promising all the consumers.
承诺所有的消费者。
To appeal this NEAR,
诉求这个NEAR，
leverage is the NDN wireless.
杠杆作用是NDN无线。
We want to leverage the NDN naturally
我们希望自然地利用NDN的优势
supports for the multicast
支持多播功能
and also combining
以及结合
this lower layer wireless technology.
这种低层无线技术。
Power for the current wireless,
当前无线电力，
the link layer still performs
链路层仍然执行
the multiple-unicast.
多播单播。
Device centric transmission rather
设备中心的传输更倾向于
than the content centric.
比内容中心更倾向于。
We perform integrate
我们执行整合
the high-performance
我们执行整合高性能的link-layer multicast into
link-layer multicast into
我们执行整合高性能的链路层组播到
the near platform to
数据平面的近端平台。
elaborate in this state for data plan of
详述此状态下的数据计划。
NDN through more automatically groups
NDN通过更加自动化的方式进行分组
the users with the same interests.
具有相同兴趣的用户。
Also performed this high
同样执行了这一高效率的链路层组播。
rate link-layer multicast.
实现了高效率的链路层组播。
The physical layer can achieve as high as
物理层可以达到高达
450 Mbps and the urinary experiments.
物理层可以达到高达450 Mbps，而尿液实验表明。
The peak application speed can be
应用层的峰值速度可以达到
greater than 120 Mbps.
应用层的峰值速度可以达到大于120 Mbps。此外，比无线，
Furthermore than the wireless,
我们还集成了加速模块
into our NEAR platform.
集成到我们的NEAR平台中。
We can support both the GPU
我们可以支持GPU和FPGA作为加速器。
All the modules are supported, for example,
所有模块都得到支持，例如，
when you want to leverage
当你想要利用
the FPGA as accelerators, all the frames,
当你想要利用FPGA作为加速器，所有的帧，
the sale and computations will be
销售和计算将会是
uploaded through the FPGA-based accelerator.
通过基于FPGA的加速器上传。
Then after the processing and the labeling,
然后在处理和标注之后，
all the contents will be published by
所有内容将由发布
the Edge to all the consumers.
所有内容将由发布者通过Edge传达给所有消费者。
We also integrated security into
我们还将安全性集成到了
the NEAR following the NDN specifications,
我们还将安全性集成到了遵循NDN规范的NEAR之中，包括了消费者认证。
which including the consumer authentication
我们还将安全性集成到了遵循NDN规范的NEAR之中，包括了消费者认证，以及完整性和
and also the integrity and
完整性和
encryptions for the AR contents,
加密了AR内容，
and also we included the access
并且我们还包括了访问权限
controls with consumers' certificates,
控制与消费者证书相关的权限，
basically giving the benefits
基本上是在提供好处
of the multicast,
的多播，
which has scaled through massive connections.
它通过大规模连接实现了扩展。
However, directly applying
但是，直接应用
the multicast through this Edge AR
通过这个Edge AR的多播
cannot have
无法拥有
the expected performance as we saw before.
我们之前所看到的预期表现。
We need to tackle the following issues
我们需要解决以下问题
during our requirements.
在我们的需求期间。
The first thing is how we
第一件事是我们如何
can handle the AR frame loss.
可以处理AR帧丢失。
The second, how we can fully leverage
第二，我们如何能够充分利用
multicasts because sometimes we
多播，因为有时我们无法找到NFET。
find the NFET cannot.
有时我们找不到NFET。
Even as the NFET have
有时我们找不到NFET，即使是当NFET有
the schemes for the interest compression.
有时我们找不到NFET，即使是当NFET有，但是它不能被利用于利息压缩的方案中。
However, it cannot be leveraged by
然而，它不能被利用来
the multiple consumers
多个消费者
asking for the same data.
要求相同的数据。
The last issue is how we design and to
最后一个问题是我们如何设计并且确保保护AR内容的安全。
secure and protags the AR contents
保护和保障AR内容的安全
for this group transmission.
为了本组传输。
For the first issue,
为了第一个问题，
first before our design,
首先在我们设计之前，
which has the traditional
在我们设计之前，像视频流命名空间这样的传统
like video streaming namespace,
像视频流命名空间，
which split the AR contents
分割AR内容
with the I-frame and P-frame.
带有I帧和P帧。
However, we find that during transmissions,
然而，我们发现在传输过程中，
the I-frame are already
the I-frame are already ~!@#$%^&*()
frequently lost and cannot
频繁丢失且无法
be received by the consumer
无法被消费者接收
and it blocks the AR playouts.
并且它阻断了AR播放。
High packet loss rates only happens
高数据包丢失率仅发生在
for the I-frames and P-frames are just fine.
对于I帧和P帧来说一切正常。
After thinking out the reason,
在思考出原因之后，
the root cause is that
在思考出原因之后，根本原因是
the average I-frame size is
平均I帧大小是
much more larger than the P-frame size,
比P帧的大小大得多，
and for the average I-frame size,
而对于平均I帧的大小来说，
it will have the 100 pace,
它将具有100步的速度，
and for the P-frame size,
对于P帧大小，
the average size is only 10 pace,
平均大小仅为10个步长，
and given the max frames only can support
并且考虑到最大帧仅能支持
the 1480 bytes for
每个数据帧，并且在
the payload sites and for each I-frame,
有效载荷位点，以及对于每个I帧，
it requires 68 frames to transmit.
它需要传输68帧。
However, for the P-frame,
然而，对于P帧来说，
it only requires seven frames.
它只需要七帧。
The multicast has lower layers,
多播拥有较低的层。
doesn't ensure these have
不确保这些具有
any retransmission schemes at lower layers.
任何在低层的重传机制。
Even when you deploy the higher layers,
即使你部署了上层协议，
the application retransmission schemes,
即使你部署了应用层重传机制，
I will still suffer from this.
我仍然会因此受苦。
Even when only one frame is
即使只有一帧
lost from the 68 frames,
从68帧中丢失，
the total I-frames cannot
从68帧中丢失的总I帧不能够成功重传，
be retransmitted successfully,
无法成功重传，
and even if we have two transmissions,
即使我们进行了两次传输，
we'll still suffer from this
我们仍将遭受这种困扰。
lower layer packet loss.
下层数据包丢失。
It requires a NEAR to have
它需要一个NEAR才能进行
this new namespace designs
这个新的命名空间设计
to organize this AR contents.
为了组织这些增强现实内容。
To solve this issues,
为了解决这些问题，
we more transfer from the IP frame like
我们更多地从IP框架转移过来，就像
this maybe through this uniform
这可能是通过这种统一方式
last chunk naming.
最后一块命名。
We just split the
我们刚刚分割了~!@#$%^&*()
AR contents with this chunk.
我们刚刚分割了~!@#$%^&*(), 随着每一块，我们有这个块的AR内容。
With each chunk, we have
随着每一块，我们有
the uniform content length and we design
随着每一块内容的统一长度，我们设计了
the following namespace for both producer
以下命名空间适用于生产者
and also the Edge to produce AR contents.
同时还适用于生产者创建AR内容的边缘计算环境。
For a producer,
对于生产者来说，
each producer will have a unique producer ID.
每个生产者都将拥有一个独特的生产者ID。
Also for the producers
同样适用于生产者。
located in the same positions,
位于相同的位置，
they will have the same group ID
它们将具有相同的组ID。
which is used for later AR functions.
它用于以后的AR功能。
In the naming, we also include
在命名中，我们也包括
the qualities, the chunk numbers,
质量、块号，
and frame types to
和帧类型来
help the applications to perform
帮助应用程序执行
more like the adaptively retransmissions
更像是自适应重传
based on the frame types.
基于帧类型。
For the AR contents, we further add
对于AR内容，我们进一步添加了
the Edge ID and the AR tasks into it,
我们将Edge ID和AR任务集成进去，
so that consumers automatically grouped
以便自动对消费者进行分组
by this AR task
通过这个增强现实任务
ask for the same configurations,
请求相同的配置，
so that it doesn't need
以免不需要
any extra information such as signaling.
任何额外的信息，比如信号。
Leveraging the naming information in
利用命名信息在
the NEAR can benefit through two aspects.
NEAR可以从两个方面受益。
The first thing is that the namespace
第一件事是命名空间
has simplified the idea of management.
简化了管理的概念。
For example, we do not
例如，我们不需要
need any extra signals.
不需要任何额外的信号。
We're more like embed
我们更像是嵌入式
the signaling over data so
数据传输中的信号传递所以
that all the consumers
所有的消费者
share the same task with
承担相同的任务
the same configurations can be
承担相同的配置可以
automatically grouped by the network and
自动由网络分组并且
doesn't need the applications
不需要应用程序来处理了。
to handle it anymore.
不再需要处理它了。
The second way is that also
第二种方式也是如此。
the namespace design can
命名空间的设计可以
benefit different AR tasks.
有利于不同的增强现实任务。
For example, in our Shareview function,
例如，在我们的Shareview功能中，
here we involve two producers,
在这里我们涉及到两个制片人，
as at in the demo.
在演示中所示。
The first producer and second producer will
第一个生产者和第二个生产者将会
be as the Edge will retrieve its own views.
将会按照Edge自身的方式来检索它的视图。
Here we have two separate views
我们这里有两个不同的视图
and then the Edge needs to
将它们组合在一起，仅需
combines the views in the same group.
将同一组中的视图组合起来。
If we do not have these namings,
如果我们没有这些命名，
we need to perform
我们需要执行
this very expensive serial processing which
我们需要执行这种非常昂贵的串行处理，它
can not support the real-time AR experience.
无法支持实时AR体验。
Give this AR grouping
无法支持实时AR体验。给这个AR分组信息在NEAR内部， Unable to support real-time AR experience. Assign this AR to a group, information inside the NEAR,
information inside the NEAR,
信息在NEAR内部，
the Edge Server can directly
边缘服务器可以直接
apply the aggregations
应用聚合操作
and the clustering based
和基于聚类的
on the namimg information.
关于命名信息。
Then after you cluster these group of frames,
然后在你对这些组帧进行聚类之后，
you can apply this feature point extraction
在这之后，你可以应用这个特征点提取，
and transformation to combine
和变换结合在一起
the two views together and publish
将这两种视角结合起来并发布
this whole panorama view and
将这整个全景视角
publish to all consumers.
发布给所有消费者。
The second issue we
第二个问题我们
faced is that we find that
面临的是我们发现
the interest compression actually
我们发现的是实际上利息压缩经常在真实实验中被忽略。
is frequently missed in the real experiments.
经常在真实实验中被忽略。
Even the NFD will compress the interest when
即使NFD在当...时也会压缩利益，
needs that have the same interests
具有相同利益的需求
extended by the consumer.
延伸至消费者。
However, if the consumers
然而，如果消费者
are now synchronized and
现在已经同步了并且
this one where you're already frequently
这个你已经经常
missed, for example,
错过了，例如，
the consumer A may ask for the latest chunk,
消费者A可能会请求最新的数据块，
the chunk 1 to the Edge and the Edge have
消费者A可能会请求最新的数据块，将数据块1传输到边缘节点，边缘节点拥有
the chunk 1 so it immediately
可以立即响应数据块1
respond with the chunk 1 data.
响应数据块1。
However, just maybe after
然而，也许就在之后
even several milliseconds,
即使是几毫秒，
the consumer B sends his chunks
消费者B发送了他的数据块
wants interests and ask for the chunk 1,
消费者B想要利益并请求数据块1，
even as they keep requesting
即使他们不断请求
the same chunks round
同样的块状物体一轮又一轮地
by round and with more consumers.
同样的块状物体一轮又一轮地, 以及有更多的消费者。
However, the address will just more
然而，地址只会更多
extend this chunk 1 multiple times
将这个数据块1多次扩展
rather than the multicast ones.
而不是多播的那些。
To solve these issues
为了解决这些问题
which blows in NEAR with
这些在附近吹拂的
these chunk prefetching schemes,
这些块预取机制，
before it's retrieving
在它检索之前
the actual AR contents,
实际的增强现实内容，
what it will do is that it will
它将会
first send this metadata interests to
首先发送这些元数据兴趣到
retrieve the latest chunk numbers from
从中检索最新的块号
the Edge plus other
边缘加上其他
maybe the stream informations.
也许是流信息。
Also, after it got the latest chunks,
此外，在获取了最新的数据块之后，
what the consumers will do is that
消费者将会做的是
it not only sends this interests
它不仅仅发送了这些兴趣
to reassure the latest chunk but retrieves
但是检索以安抚最新的数据块
future chunks and also
未来的数据块以及还有
maintains the outstanding interest window.
保持突出的兴趣窗口。
For example, in this demo,
例如，在这个演示中，
we showed as it
例如，在这个演示中，我们展示了它如何维护窗口大小
was maintaining the window size
在维护窗口大小
30 and after it's got this chunk number 1,
30号之后它得到了这个块编号1，
the latest chance number,
最新的机会号码，
it will send the interest to retrieve
它将发送兴趣以检索
the future 11-40 chunks
未来的11-40个数据块
and directly send all the interests
并直接发送所有的兴趣包。
to the Edge Server.
发送到边缘服务器。
Whenever in the future that chunks
未来的某个时刻，那些数据块
11 is produced, for example,
将会被AR处理生成，例如，
by the AR processing
将会被AR处理
then the chunky 11 can be
然后，chunky 11可以被
directly multicast to all the consumers
可以直接多播给所有消费者
without the multiple transmissions.
无需多次传输。
Then after the consumers, for example,
那么在消费者之后，例如，
A and B receive this data
A和B接收到这个数据
and you can send this chunk
并且你可以发送这个数据块
41 to move this window
将这个窗口移动到41位置。
forward and send new interest.
转发并发送新的兴趣。
This one is more like,
这个更像是，
we do not need
我们不需要
a very strict synchronizations between
非常严格的同步操作
all the consumers and we can enjoy
所有消费者我们都可以享受
this multicast benefits
这种多播的好处
for most of the cases.
在大多数情况下。
We also deploy this
我们也部署了这个
application retransmissions.
即使是应用程序重传。
Even for the application retransmissions,
即使是应用程序重传，
we are all using the multicast because
我们都在使用多播，因为
the lower layers may miss
下层可能会丢失
the similar packet loss at
下层可能会丢失类似的数据包
the lower layer and
下层并且
also the retransmissions can
也可以进行重传
also benefit multiple users packet loss.
也能够使得多个用户受益，减少数据包丢失。
Last issue we'll tackle is how
上一期我们要解决的问题是如何
we ensure the AR content security.
我们确保增强现实内容的安全性。
Integrate this security into the NEAR
将这种安全性整合到NEAR中
following the NDN specifications and
遵循NDN规范并且
all the data contents from both sides
所有双方的数据内容
like the mobile to Server
像移动设备对服务器
and also the Edge Server
以及边缘服务器
to mobile are signed with
移动端的签名是由
the producer's certificates
制作人的证书
using this RSA signature.
使用这个RSA签名。
This ensures that the packets are produced by
这确保了数据包是由
the valid producers and
合法生产者所发送的，
also after receiving the data,
还有，在接收到数据之后，
the consumers will check the certificates
消费者将会检查证书。
whether corresponding keys are
是否相应的密钥是
in the local key cache.
在本地密钥缓存中。
If it doesn't zero, it
如果它不归零，它会
will go to the KeyLocator to
去KeyLocator寻找
fetch the keys to
去KeyLocator寻找keys以
validate the data's integrity.
验证数据的完整性。
To ensure the security furthermore,
为了进一步确保安全性，
we act the encryption and
我们执行加密操作并且
access controls for the AR contents.
我们为AR内容设置访问控制。
For all the traffic
对于所有的流量
from the producer to Edge,
从生产者到边缘节点，
we encrypt the data
我们对数据进行加密。
with pre-shared content keys.
使用预共享的内容密钥。
For the Edge to consumers,
为了将边缘计算带给消费者，
we perform this two-stage
我们执行这两阶段
like the content encryption,
像内容加密一样，
learn from the NDN-NAC.
从NDN-NAC中学习。
The two-stage means that first,
两阶段意味着首先，
the consumers will send the interest to
消费者将发送兴趣至
retrieve this content keys
检索这些内容关键字
and also in the interest,
我们还将考虑消费者的利益，
we will include the consumer's ID
我们还将包括消费者的身份证号。
with these public keys.
我们还将包括消费者的身份证号。与这些公钥一起。The Edge Servers can check whether
The Edge Servers can check whether
边缘服务器可以检查是否
these IDs and public keys
这些ID和公钥
are in this access control list.
在这个访问控制列表中。
If it's allowed to access
在这个访问控制列表中，如果被允许访问，
this specific task,
这个特定任务，
the corresponding content key for this task
将会发送给移动消费者的相应内容关键字。
will be sent to the mobile consumer.
将会发送给移动消费者。
would pick like this.
会像这样选择。
This key will also be encrypted with
这个密钥也将被加密。
the public key shared by this consumer and
这个消费者共享的公钥，
later the consumer can extract
后来，消费者可以提取
this content key with his private key and
他的私钥和这个内容密钥一起
uses this content key to decode
使用这个内容密钥来解码
all the group content like
所有群组内容类似于
the AR contents in this specific AR task.
这个特定AR任务中的AR内容。
All the content keys we also
我们还有所有的内容关键。
update the IV every time to ensure
更新 IV（初始化向量）以确保
that the packet cannot
数据包无法
suffer from the key reuse attack.
遭受密钥重用攻击。
Then we will show a demo video
然后我们将展示一个演示视频。
about our platform,
关于我们的平台，
and in this demo prototype we use
在这个演示原型中，我们使用了
Ubuntu 18 as the Edge server
Ubuntu 18 作为边缘服务器
and with the Intel i7 CPU,
配备了英特尔 i7 CPU，
with the RTX 2080S GPU.
配备了 RTX 2080S GPU。
Also for the access points,
配备了 RTX 2080S GPU。对于接入点，we're using two access points with the N750。
we're using two access points with the N750
我们正在使用两个配备了N750的接入点。
and also the AC 1750 routers,
和AC 1750路由器，
which support the wireless with
支持无线连接的
the high rate link-layer multicast.
高速率链路层组播。
Also, we involve different mobile clients
同时，我们还涉及了不同的移动客户端。
as the producer and also the consumers,
作为生产者同时也是消费者，
including the Google Pixel phones and
包括谷歌Pixel手机和
also the Xiaomi phones
也包括小米手机
with different Androids like
包括不同的安卓设备，比如
the smartphones and all things
智能手机和所有的东西
are enroute and with
在途中并且与
the commercial products and
商业产品和
here is the demo we want to show.
这是我们想要展示的演示。
First, we show the
首先，我们展示了
NEAR basic platform setting and
NEAR基础平台设置和
the Edge server is running on
边缘服务器正在运行在
Ubuntu server and also
Ubuntu服务器也在
the access point are connected
接入点已连接
to the servers through a switch.
通过交换机连接到服务器。
In the NEAR platform,
在NEAR平台上，
the producer key publishing
生产者密钥发布
the latest frames from each camera view.
最新的每个摄像机视角的画面。
For example, here we show
例如，我们在这里展示
the producer points to Street View,
制作人指向街景图，
and the Edge server will
以及边缘服务器将会
retrieve the street view from the producers.
从制片人那里获取街景视图。
The Edge server will process
边缘服务器将会处理
the stream with the Yolo modulus
流使用Yolo模块
and with the accelerators
和加速器一起
to achieve this real-time processing.
为了实现这种实时处理。
Also the NEAR support both the GPUs and
同时，NEAR还支持GPU和
FPGAs to support
AI acceleration tasks, including this Yolo and open post [inaudible] tasks.
this Yolo and open post [inaudible] tasks.
这个Yolo和开放式岗位[听不清]任务。
After the processing,
经过处理后，
the consumers could retrieve
消费者可以检索
the latest AR streams with
最新的AR直播流
the corresponding naming and
对应的命名和
according to the namespace before.
根据之前的命名空间。
All the contents will be
所有内容将会
transmitted through the link-layer multicast.
通过链路层多播传输。
As we can see, all the contents
可以看出，所有内容
only need to transmit once
只需要传输一次
and all the consumers can
并且所有的消费者都可以
receive it at the same time.
接收它。
Then we introduce the several AR modules
然后我们介绍几个AR模块。
supported by our platform.
由我们的平台支持。
As we can see, we first
由我们首先可以看到，
show that the Edge can leverage in
表明Edge可以利用在
their namings to group consumers interests
将它们的命名用于对消费者兴趣进行分组
and performs corresponding processing.
并进行相应的处理。
By retrieving the latest
通过检索最新的
published like the real time camera stream,
发布就像实时摄像机流。
the Edge perform this object recognition and
边缘设备执行这种物体识别并且
published real-time results to
发布实时结果给
all the consumers with link-layer multicast.
向所有使用链路层组播的消费者发布实时结果。
Also, we support the face detection task.
我们还支持面部检测任务。
Leveraging the face mask
我们还支持面部检测任务。利用面部遮罩，借助加速器，
with the accelerators,
我们还支持面部检测任务。利用面部遮罩，借助加速器，借助加速器，Edge服务器可以支持，
the Edge servers can support,
Edge服务器可以支持，
process multiple faces,
处理多个面孔，
even hundreds of faces at the same time,
即使是同时处理数百张面孔，
and with the real-time experiment
和实时实验一起进行
supporting the Edge AR.
支持边缘增强现实（Edge AR）。
As we can see here in the view,
正如我们在这里的视图中所看到的，
we also have a content like
我们也有类似的内容
the consumers here and which can
我们这里的消费者以及可以显示视频是
show that the videos are
显示视频是
transmitted from the producer to
从生产者传输到
the consumer with the real-time experiments.
消费者提供实时实验数据。
The OpenPose module provides
OpenPose模块提供
this jointly detection of the human body,
这是对人体的联合检测，
head, and facial and full key points
头部、面部以及完整的关键点
and even further,
以及更进一步，
we can include all this informations
我们可以包含所有这些信息
into the namings so that
进入命名中，以便
all the consumers can
所有消费者可以
retrieve the informations
获取信息
they want according
他们想要根据
to the naming information.
他们想要根据命名信息。
Leveraging the ADSR with NDI
利用ADSR与NDI技术结合
the mobile can detect the human skeletons.
手机能够检测到人体骨骼。
Here we show the AR overlays
这里我们展示了增强现实叠加层
and the AR overlay video
与增强现实叠加层视频相结合
just detects the markers in the sense,
仅检测场景中的标记，
and puts videos as overlay on it.
并在其上叠加视频。
This one is targeted as some
这个是针对一些
advertisement scenarios so that for example,
广告场景，以便例如，
the motion can perform
该动作可以执行
some AR advertisements
一些增强现实广告
on the specific products.
在特定的产品上。
Also we include this 3D model rendering and
此外，我们还提供了这个3D模型渲染服务，以及在特定的产品上，所有这些3D模型都是渲染过的。
all these 3D models are rendered
所有这些3D模型都是渲染过的。
as the edge adds server sides.
边缘增加了服务器端。
For example, after
例如，在
recognizing the market position,
识别市场定位，
it can render the 3D models with
它可以渲染3D模型，
corresponding angles and the consumers
相应的角度和消费者
can move the different angles.
可以移动不同的角度。
According to the producer's view,
根据制作人的观点，
it can change in the different angles to show
它可以在不同的角度变换以展示
that this 3D products for
这些3D产品为了
the advertisements and also
用于广告宣传以及未来产品展示。
for future product displaying.
用于未来产品展示。
For the shareview function,
为了共享视图功能，
we include multiple producers
我们包括了多个生产者。
and multiple consumers.
和多个消费者。
For example, here we have
例如，这里我们有
two producers inside the view,
两个生产者位于视图内部，
and the server-side,
以及服务器端，
we retrieve the views
我们检索视图
from post the left side,
从帖子左侧，
the left consumer, and right
左侧的消费者和右边的
side the right producer.
侧的右边生产者。
After this, grouped by
之后，分组由
this naming and you will
这种命名方式，你将会
perform the feature point extraction
执行特征点提取
and combine the two videos together.
并将两个视频合并在一起。
Then all the shareview
然后将所有的shareview
will be just published through
将会直接发布通过
the multicast to all the consumers
将会直接发布给所有的消费者
to have this multiple producer,
将会有这多个生产者，
multiple consumer support
支持多个消费者
with real time processing.
支持实时处理。
The chroma key video which is to support
实时抠图的视频需求支持
this processing from producer,
来自制作人的这一处理过程，
we add the chroma keys
我们添加了色键。
at the Edge server side,
在边缘服务器端，
and then we can locate it
然后我们就可以定位它
as the consumer side on this real objects,
作为这些真实物体的消费者端，
for example, the stage to support
例如，用来支持舞台的
this interactive operas applications.
这些交互式歌剧应用程序。
We also compare the performance
我们还比较了性能
under the multiple consumers to test
在多个消费者下进行测试
the performance of this link-layer multicast
这个链路层多播的性能
and also combining with
以及结合
a whole NEAR platform.
整个NEAR平台。
As we can see, to test this,
我们可以看到，为了测试这个，
we want to compare the
我们想要比较~!@#$%^&*()
performance with the NEAR,
我们想要比较~!@#$%^&*()的性能与单播流的性能。
with the unicast streaming.
与单播流相比较。
We using the same videos
我们使用相同的视频。
to show the difference.
为了展示差异。
Using this video is to 2K source and also we
使用这个视频是为了2K源，同时我们也~!@#$%^&*()
have these four consumers involved in it.
这涉及到这四个消费者。
We have a 60 Mbps background traffic to
我们有一个60 Mbps的背景流量来
simulate the very heavy congestions.
模拟非常严重的拥堵情况。
As we can see, for the NEAR platform
我们可以看到，对于NEAR平台来说
can keep publishing
可以继续发布
the 2K sources that are very fluent
这些非常流畅的2K资源
and with them in here very high [inaudible].
和它们在这里非常高[听不清]。
For the unicast,
对于单播，
is suffer from the congestion
受到拥塞的困扰
and sometimes the resources
有时候资源
cannot be delivered to
无法按时送达给
the consumers on time
无法按时送达给消费者
and we're stuck in there.
我们被困在那里了。
Even for these four consumers
即使对于这四位消费者来说
with heavy backgrounds.
即使对于这四位消费者来说，他们有着深厚的背景。直到我们将更多消费者纳入其中，
Until we add more consumers into it,
直到我们将更多消费者纳入其中，
the NEAR will not add further [inaudible].
NEAR将不会增加进一步的[听不清]。
Only some few extra overheads
只有一些额外的开销
will cost by the retransmission plus
将因重传而产生的成本加上
a major overhead like the video transmissions
像视频传输这样的主要开销
because we're using only multicasts ones
因为我们只使用多播模式
and doesn't like unicasts
因为我们只使用多播模式，不喜欢单播模式，可扩展性非常高。
the scalability is much
高于我们的平台。
worse than our platform.
比我们的平台差。
We will release our closing our websites.
我们将关闭我们的网站。
We are glad to introduce
我们很高兴介绍
our platform and welcome for
我们的平台欢迎来自~!@#$%^&*()
[inaudible] to leveraging our platform
利用我们的平台[听不清]
and also we can design more modules into it.
我们还可以设计更多的模块进去。
Thanks. I'm glad to
谢谢。我很高兴。
answer any questions if you have.
如果你有任何问题，请回答。
>> This is very cool.
>> 这真的很酷。
Thank you. I have a quick question.
谢谢。我有个简单的问题。
When you were talking about the scalability,
当你谈论可扩展性时，
I think you compared unicast and multicast.
我认为你比较了单播和多播。
Is there anything that also
~!@#$%^&*()
looks at the number of consumers?
看消费者的数量？
Because I think in
因为我认为在
your slide you talked about four,
你在幻灯片中提到了四个，
would this be affected at all if let's
这是否会受到任何影响，如果我们假设
say the number of consumers go up to 20?
消费者的数量增加到20人？
>> Yeah. Due to
是的，由于我们设备数量的限制，
the limitation of our device numbers,
我们设备数量的限制，
we only have six phones
我们只有六部手机。
at most and so that we
最多，以便我们
connect all the phones onto the server,
将所有手机连接到服务器上，
and what we see is that actually,
我们实际上看到的是，
the throughput doesn't increase a lot.
吞吐量并没有大幅增加。
But doesn't like the unicast
但这并不像单播
when we add six consumers in there,
当我们在那里增加六个消费者时，
the throughput will be
吞吐量将会是
six times as the original one.
吞吐量将会是原来的六倍。
But for our NEAR is more like maintaining
但对于我们的NEAR来说，更像是保持着
a similar throughput all the time.
始终保持类似的吞吐量。
>> Appreciate it.
>> 非常感谢。
>> Thank you. [OVERLAPPING]
>> 非常感谢。[同时说话]
>> Back to you [inaudible].
~!@#$%^&*()
>> Thank you very much,
>> 非常感谢您，
Tamer and all the speakers.
塔梅尔和所有的演讲者。
We are on time for the 20-minute break.
我们准时开始20分钟的休息时间。
It's almost 3:30.
快到3点半了。
We will be back in 20 minutes
我们将在20分钟后回来。
at 3:50, for session 4.
在3点50分，第4场会议。
We'll see you all in 20 minutes. Thanks.
我们20分钟后见。谢谢。